<row Id="23158" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2658" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:42:50.937" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;From personal experience, svn would be my recommendation.  You can even use a service like &lt;a href=&quot;http://beanstalkapp.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Beanstalk&lt;/a&gt; that offers free accounts (with limits obviously, but sufficient for any smallish project) to test the waters.  But as others have said, git is superior and is likely worth looking into.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2272" OwnerDisplayName="jonezy" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:42:50.937" CommunityOwnedDate="2008-09-23T06:50:43.100" />
<row Id="23162" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23098" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:45:27.123" Score="3" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Having your own license (usually a&#xA;  variant on one of the existing ones)&#xA;  allows you full control over it. I&#xA;  suspect that things like the huge&#xA;  change between GPL2 and GPL3&#xA;  (especially if you deal with web&#xA;  services) make people leery of&#xA;  licensing with an agreement outside of&#xA;  one's control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think this is true to some extent.  However, when you license under the GPL, you have the option to say, &quot;Version 2&quot;, &quot;Version 2 or later&quot;.  If you're leary about how the license may change in the future, you are free to just say it is licensed under that specific version.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:45:27.123" />
<row Id="23164" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="21174" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:45:42.363" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://dialect.openmodeling.net/downloads&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Open Dialect&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.salasaga.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Salasaga&lt;/a&gt; seem to be the main FOSS IDEs for this. They should both be cross-platform with mono and GTK respectively (not completely sure about OSX). I think Open Dialect also does AIR.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've no idea how they compare to the commercial IDEs so you might have to try each of them to compare.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1352" OwnerDisplayName="marcas" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:45:42.363" />
<row Id="23166" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23179" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:46:09.010" Score="40" ViewCount="3995" Body="&lt;p&gt;I like to study languages outside my comfort zone, but I've had a hard time finding a place to start for functional languages.  I heard a lot of good things about &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0070004846&quot;&gt;Structure and Interpretations of Computer Programs&lt;/a&gt;, but when I tried to read through it a couple of years ago it just seemed to whiz over my head.  I do way better with books than web sites, but when I visit the local book store the books on LISP look kind of scary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what's a good starting point?  My goal is to be able to use a functional programming language to solve simple problems in 6 months or so, and the ability to move to more advanced topics, recognize when a functional language is the right tool for the job, and use the language to solve more problems over the course of 2-3 years.  I like books that are heavy on examples but also include challenges to work through.  Does such a thing exist for functional languages?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2547" OwnerDisplayName="Owen Pellegrin" LastEditorUserId="2134" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2008-08-23T14:49:43.517" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T20:50:49.573" Title="What's a good beginning text on functional programming?" Tags="&lt;functional-programming&gt;&lt;lisp&gt;&lt;scheme&gt;" AnswerCount="15" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="28" />
<row Id="23168" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23031" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:46:55.387" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;A good key to remember is &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&quot;Test early, test often and test again, when you think you are done&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1311" OwnerDisplayName="Pascal" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:46:55.387" />
<row Id="23169" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:47:03.610" Score="2" ViewCount="3218" Body="&lt;p&gt;When using Groovy MarkupBuilder, I have places where I need to output text into the document, or call a function which outputs text into the document.  Currently, I'm using the undefined tag &quot;text&quot; to do the output.  Is there a better way to write this code?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;li{&#xA;  text(&quot;${type.getAlias()} blah blah &quot;)&#xA;  function1(type.getXYZ())&#xA;  if (type instanceof Class1) {&#xA;    text(&quot; implements &quot;)&#xA;    ft.getList().each{ &#xA;      if (it == '') return&#xA;      text(it) &#xA;      if (!function2(type, it)) text(&quot;, &quot;)&#xA;    }&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="philvarner" LastEditorUserId="543969" LastEditDate="2012-11-15T03:07:04.950" LastActivityDate="2012-11-15T03:07:04.950" Title="HTML using Groovy MarkupBuilder, how do I elegantly mix tags and text?" Tags="&lt;html&gt;&lt;groovy&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
<row Id="23174" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23001" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:50:41.977" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I guess the tool I was looking for was under my nose the whole time!  I've used Maintenance Plans for backups but I think I set those up at least 4 years ago or more, long before I knew anything about shrinking files and defragging indexes.  Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2505" OwnerDisplayName="upheaval" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:50:41.977" />
<row Id="23175" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:50:52.477" Score="1" ViewCount="74" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is mostly geared toward desktop application developers.  How do I design a caching block which plays nicely with the GC?  How do I tell the GC that I have just done a cache sweep and it is time to do a GC?  How do I get an accurate measure of when it is time to do a cache sweep?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are there any prebuilt caching schemes which I could borrow some ideas from?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1490" OwnerDisplayName="Nick" LastEditorUserId="1559" LastEditorDisplayName="Scott Dorman" LastEditDate="2009-02-11T20:59:24.030" LastActivityDate="2010-01-21T12:02:24.660" Title="Caching Schemes for Managed Languages" Tags="&lt;caching&gt;&lt;garbage-collection&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
<row Id="23176" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23181" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:50:54.660" Score="5" ViewCount="878" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am a C/C++ programmer professionally, but I've created a couple of personal web sites using PHP and MySQL. They're pretty basic, and I'd like to jazz them up using Ajax, but I've never done any Ajax. I've done all the development so far manually, i.e. no IDE or anything like that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have suggestions on Ajax development environments that can help me? Shareware or freeware would be preferable as I'd find it hard to justify spending more than a minimal amount of money on this...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1821" OwnerDisplayName="Graeme" LastEditorUserId="1086697" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2013-04-29T19:33:29.490" LastActivityDate="2013-04-29T19:33:29.490" Title="Suggestions on Ajax development environment for PHP" Tags="&lt;php&gt;&lt;javascript&gt;&lt;ajax&gt;&lt;ide&gt;" AnswerCount="6" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="23177" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:51:50.680" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you want an IDE, try &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aptana.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Aptana Studio&lt;/a&gt;. It supports HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, XML, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, and more....&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:51:50.680" />
<row Id="23178" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23194" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:52:14.690" Score="1" ViewCount="1085" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there a .NET variable that returns the &quot;All Users&quot; directory?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1632" OwnerDisplayName="Maudite" LastEditorUserId="1477076" LastEditDate="2012-08-11T16:14:27.213" LastActivityDate="2012-08-11T16:14:35.073" Title="&quot;All Users&quot; Folder" Tags="&lt;.net&gt;&lt;io&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
<row Id="23179" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:52:28.230" Score="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ccs.neu.edu/home/matthias/BTLS/&quot;&gt;The Little Schemer&lt;/a&gt; teaches recursion really well, and it's fun and simple to read. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also liked &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scheme.com/tspl3/&quot;&gt;The Scheme Programming Language&lt;/a&gt; for a broader introduction into the language. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1797" OwnerDisplayName="mk" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:52:28.230" />
<row Id="23181" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:54:07.353" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;As T.O. says, try Aptana. There's a very good free version, and they really push the AJAX. They even have Jaxer, an &quot;AJAX Server&quot; that they're working on. If nothing else, the plugins are great, and, other than a few quirks, I really like working in it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1344" OwnerDisplayName="Brian Warshaw" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:54:07.353" />
<row Id="23182" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:54:30.330" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;First off, make sure you understand the basics of the HTTP protocol. Then learn how the javascript httpXmlRequest function works. Once you've covered those, pick an Ajax library - prototype is good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then look at a few examples, and follow the API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Job done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I seriously have no idea how they manage to write entire books on this subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: Why vote me down? Learning the basics first, leads to a much better understanding of the way it works. And yes, I believe Jeff should learn C too ;-P&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1951" OwnerDisplayName="mercutio" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:54:30.330" />
<row Id="23183" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:54:37.193" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Rolling your own AJAX has become somewhat outdated in the presence of Javascript libraries like Prototype and JQuery.  I would recommend looking into one of those libraries (Jeff used JQuery for SO and he's been really impressed with it from what I understand).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as a development environment goes, I don't know that there's much.  A typical text editor with syntax highlighting would do the trick for writing (like Notepad++).  For debugging, take a look at the Firebug extension for Firefox (though if you use JQuery, a debugging tool may not be as useful).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="271" OwnerDisplayName="Justin Bennett" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:54:37.193" />
<row Id="23184" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:54:53.683" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I found &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0262560992&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Little Schemer&lt;/a&gt; a great, great introduction to functional programming.  It's entirely based on simple, bite sized examples which are built up upon as the book goes on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="156" OwnerDisplayName="Joe Shaw" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:54:53.683" />
<row Id="23185" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:55:08.927" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Haskell is a very good functional programming language for beginners. Someone had asked about good resources for Haskell, so I will point you &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16918/beginners-guide-to-haskell#16951&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a good book on Functional Programming, I would recommend &quot;Functional Programming: Practice and Theory&quot; by  Bruce J. Maclennan. &lt;br&gt;&#xA;It is however required that you brush up on your Set Theory and Logic before giving it a read. It includes examples in LISP, Haskell and other languages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1311" OwnerDisplayName="Pascal" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:55:08.927" />
<row Id="23187" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:55:21.407" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aptana.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Aptana&lt;/a&gt; is supposedly a decent IDE for Javascript development. I myself just use Eclipse and a decent javascript framework like &lt;a href=&quot;http://jquery.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt; that has an easy syntax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="204" OwnerDisplayName="dragonmantank" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:55:21.407" />
<row Id="23188" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:55:31.653" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you have experience with .NET, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apress.com/book/view/9781590598504&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Expert #F&lt;/a&gt; is good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;F# is derived from OCaml.  Lisp is more pure as functional languages go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="580" OwnerDisplayName="Brian Leahy" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:55:31.653" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23190" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25002" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:56:04.850" Score="3" ViewCount="1029" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am working on a function to establish the entropy of a distribution.  It uses a copula, if any are familiar with that.  I need to sum up the values in the array based on which dimensions are &quot;cared about.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example:  Consider the following example... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&#xA;Dimension 0 (across)&#xA;_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _&#xA;|_ 0 _|_ 0 _|_ 0 _|_ 2 _|  Dimension 1&#xA;|_ 1 _|_ 0 _|_ 2 _|_ 0 _|   (down)&#xA;|_ 0 _|_ 3 _|_ 0 _|_ 6 _|&#xA;|_ 0 _|_ 0 _|_ 0 _|_ 0 _|&#xA;&#xA;I &quot;care about&quot; dimension 0 only, and &quot;don't care&quot; about the rest (dim 1).&#xA;Summing this array with the above specifications will&#xA;&quot;collapse&quot; the &quot;stacks&quot; of dimension 1 down to a single 4 x 1 array:&#xA;&#xA;_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ &#xA;|_ 1 _|_ 3 _|_ 2 _|_ 8 _|&#xA;&#xA;This can then be summed, or have any operation performed.&#xA;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I need to do this with an array of 'n' dimensions, which could feasibly be 20. Also, I need to be able to do this, caring about certain dimensions, and collapsing the rest.  I am having an especially hard time with this because I cant visualize 20 dimensions :p . If anyone could help me set up some c/c++ code to collapse/sum, I would be very very grateful.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Update:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just got home.  Here is some info to answer your questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sorry for rolling back the edits, I was hoping when I clicked roll-back it would show me the changes so I could see what I messed up, a bit like wikipedia.  This wasn't the case, as I found out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;@jeff - What doesnt make sense?  I am using this great service for (what I think is) a legit reason.  I want to get better at my hobby, which is all it is, as I am in high school.  Many of my posts regard implementing a genetic algorithm (This post, sparsearray, rank an array, pointer manipulation).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I am using a sparse array representation, as it is possible to exceed the number of molecules in the universe using a traditional (dense) array.  For now, the implementation of the sparsearray itself doesnt matter a whole lot, as I am working to make it work with a standard array before going to a sparse representation.  For those who havent seen my previous questions, I am using a binary search tree as the structure to contain the sparse array points, and a &quot;driver&quot; function to traverse the tree as necessary, returning whatever the function is designed to do.  This is flexible, so I can accomodate a lot of different methods of accessing the array. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The structure is a hypercube, and the number of dimensions is specified at run time, as well as the length of each dimension (which are all the same, as it is a hypercube).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone for your imput.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="522" OwnerDisplayName="Ed" LastEditorUserId="96780" LastEditorDisplayName="Gaius" LastEditDate="2013-07-23T14:41:49.443" LastActivityDate="2013-07-23T14:41:49.443" Title="How Does One Sum Dimensions of an Array Specified at Run-Time?" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;&lt;c&gt;&lt;arrays&gt;&lt;dynamics&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23192" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23176" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:56:54.723" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.modernmethod.com/sajax/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Sajax&lt;/a&gt; is another good toolkit with PHP support.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mostly though I prefer to use a Javascript framework like &lt;a href=&quot;http://jquery.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Jquery&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prototypejs.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Prototype&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="305" OwnerDisplayName="Mark Biek" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:56:54.723" />
<row Id="23193" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:56:54.897" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;SICP is a great book. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is probably my bias, but I thought ocaml was pretty easy to get into. You have the option of programming in a few different styles until you're completely comfortable. I &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22873/language-referencestutorials-for-popular-languages#22940&quot;&gt;posted a bunch of links&lt;/a&gt; to Haskell and Ocaml references that &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; books, with examples et cetera that seem right up your alley.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you prefer Lisp, you can try to power through the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ic.unicamp.br/~meidanis/courses/mc336/2006s2/funcional/L-99_Ninety-Nine_Lisp_Problems.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;99-problems in Lisp&lt;/a&gt;(which you can do in any language, really), or you can watch the &lt;a href=&quot;http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=5546836985338782440&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;lectures&lt;/a&gt; from the people who wrote SICP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Further down the road, get a hold of &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=SxPzSTcTalAC&amp;amp;dq=purely+functional+data+structures&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Purely Functional Data Structures&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, as it'll get into the hard-core deep design and considerations you have to take into account in functional languages --it uses ML (which ocaml derived from).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" OwnerDisplayName="nlucaroni" LastEditorUserId="157" LastEditorDisplayName="nlucaroni" LastEditDate="2011-12-05T20:50:49.573" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T20:50:49.573" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="23194" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23178" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:57:25.753" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;You'll want to use the system.environment variables.  Most of the predefined ones are &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/system.environment.getenvironmentvariable.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;shown here&lt;/a&gt;.  For the &quot;All Users&quot; you would use&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;System.Environment.GetEnvironmentVariable(&quot;ALLUSERSPROFILE&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know I got a lot of upmods and a correct answer for my other stuff, but this actually works. where as the other &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms933062.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;environment variables&lt;/a&gt; I linked to previously don't seem to work with that function call.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastEditorUserId="1477076" LastEditorDisplayName="Kibbee" LastEditDate="2012-08-11T16:14:35.073" LastActivityDate="2012-08-11T16:14:35.073" />
<row Id="23196" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:58:07.967" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Actually, by colllapsing the colums you already summed them, so the dimension doesn't matter at all for your example. Did I miss something or did you?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:58:07.967" />
<row Id="23197" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:58:28.573" Score="6" ViewCount="8035" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a library that reads/writes to a USB-device using CreateFile() API. The device happens to implement the HID-device profile, such that it's compatible with Microsoft's HID class driver.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some other application installed on the system is opening the device in read/write mode with no share mode. Which prevents my library (and anything that consumes it) from working with the device. I suppose that's the rub with being an HID-compatible device -- other driver software (mice, controllers, PHIDGETS, etc) can be uncooperative. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the device file path is of the form: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&#xA;1: &quot;\\?\hid#hpqremhiddevice&amp;col01#5&amp;21ff20e7&amp;0&amp;0000#{4d1e55b2-f16f-11cf-88cb-001111000030}&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;2: &quot;\\?\hid#vid_045e&amp;pid_0023#7&amp;34aa9ece&amp;0&amp;0000#{4d1e55b2-f16f-11cf-88cb-001111000030}&quot;.&#xA;&#xA;3: &quot;\?\hid#vid_056a&amp;pid_00b0&amp;col01#6&amp;5b05f29&amp;0&amp;0000#{4d1e55b2-f16f-11cf-88cb-001111000030}&quot;.&#xA;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And I'm trying to open it using code, like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;//  First, open it with minimum permissions, this device may not be ours.&#xA;//  we'll re-open it later in read/write&#xA;hid_device_ref = CreateFile(&#xA;    device_path, GENERIC_READ,&#xA;    0, NULL, OPEN_EXISTING,&#xA;    FILE_ATTRIBUTE_NORMAL, NULL);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've considered a tool like FileMon or Process Monitor from SysInternals. But I can't seem to get it to report usage on device file handles like the one listed above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2146" LastEditorUserId="1219" LastEditorDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T19:14:40.063" LastActivityDate="2009-04-09T18:48:39.570" Title="Find out which process has an exclusive lock on a USB device handle" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;&lt;winapi&gt;&lt;usb&gt;&lt;hid&gt;&lt;devices&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="23198" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:58:47.903" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have heard good things about &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0201342758&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Haskell Functional Programming&lt;/a&gt;, but I also found this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/LISP-Functional-Programming-Books/lm/36GEU8N3B2JPW&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; of functional programming books at amazon that might be helpful to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2328" OwnerDisplayName="Craig H" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:58:47.903" />
<row Id="23199" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23124" CreationDate="2008-08-22T18:59:28.523" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://developer.yahoo.com/yui/connection/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;YUI Connection Manager&lt;/a&gt; allows you to introduce slowdown in your Javascript to test AJAX against latency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="204" OwnerDisplayName="dragonmantank" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T18:59:28.523" />
<row Id="23201" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23031" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:00:10.020" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;We don't do TDD here (though some have advocated it), but our rule is that you're supposed to check your unit tests in with your changes. It doesn't always happen, but it's easy to go back and look at a specific changeset and see whether or not tests were written.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="517" OwnerDisplayName="Adam V" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:00:10.020" />
<row Id="23202" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23178" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:00:15.777" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Or, &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Environment.GetFolderPath(Environment.SpecialFolder.CommonApplicationData)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can then pass this result to System.IO.Directory.GetParent() to get the root &quot;All Users&quot; folder.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1875" OwnerDisplayName="Peter Meyer" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:00:15.777" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23203" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:00:50.720" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I really like Thompson’s “Haskell: The Craft of Functional Programming” because it’s well written and Haskell allows an easier start than other functional languages while being completely pure (unlike Lisp or Scheme).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:00:50.720" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23205" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:02:09.297" Score="2" ViewCount="80" Body="&lt;p&gt;Besides &quot;no connection&quot;, what other failure modes should I test for?  How do I simulate a high-latency link, an unreliable link, or all the other sorts of crazy stuff that will undoubtedly happen &quot;in the wild&quot;?  How about wireless applications--how do I test the performance in a less-than-ideal WL environment?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1490" OwnerDisplayName="Nick" LastActivityDate="2008-08-31T09:27:43.477" Title="Boundary Tests For a Networked App" Tags="&lt;testing&gt;&lt;networking&gt;&lt;wireless&gt;" AnswerCount="5" />
<row Id="23206" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23102" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:03:40.027" Score="25" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.owasp.org/index.php/Main_Page&quot;&gt;OWASP&lt;/a&gt; keeps a list of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.owasp.org/index.php/Category:OWASP_Top_Ten_Project&quot;&gt;Top 10&lt;/a&gt; web attacks to watch our for, in addition to a ton of other useful security information for web development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="204" OwnerDisplayName="dragonmantank" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:03:40.027" />
<row Id="23207" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22976" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:03:43.320" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Javascript doesn't really have namespace or packages like other languages. Instead it has closures. If you have an application that consists of multiple functions, variables and objects, then you should put them inside a single global object. This will have the same effect as a namespace. &#xA;For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&#xA;var namespace = {&#xA;  this.foo: function(){&#xA;    ...&#xA;  },&#xA;  this.foo.prototype.getLength: function(){&#xA;    ...&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You could also create a set of nested objects and simulate packages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;loadPackage = function(){&#xA;  var path = arguments[0];&#xA;  for(var i=1; i&amp;lt;arguments.length; i++){&#xA;    if(!path[arguments[i]]){&#xA;      path[arguments[i]] = {};&#xA;    }&#xA;    path = path[arguments[i]];&#xA;  }&#xA;  return path;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;loadPackage(this, &quot;com&quot;, &quot;google&quot;, &quot;mail&quot;) = {&#xA;  username: &quot;gundersen&quot;,&#xA;  login: function(password){&#xA;    ...&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;this.com.google.mail.login(&quot;mySecretPassword&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1585" OwnerDisplayName="Marius" LastEditorUserId="1585" LastEditDate="2009-09-12T09:45:47.953" LastActivityDate="2009-09-12T09:45:47.953" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23208" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19173" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:03:51.183" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Downside? It's fairly limited - you trigger a &quot;GET&quot; request and get back some script that's executed. You don't get error handling if your server throws an error, so you need to wrap all errors in JSON as well. You can't really cancel or retry the request. You're at the mercy of the various browser author opinions of &quot;correct&quot; behavior for dynamically-generated &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tags. Debugging is somewhat more difficult. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, i've used it on occasion, and haven't suffered. YMMV.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="811" OwnerDisplayName="Shog9" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:03:51.183" />
<row Id="23209" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="26180" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:03:52.507" Score="0" ViewCount="5944" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm building an application against some legacy, third party libraries, and having problems with the linking stage.  I'm trying to compile with Visual Studio 9.  My compile command is:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;cl -DNT40 -DPOMDLL -DCRTAPI1=&lt;em&gt;cdecl&#xA; -DCRTAPI2=cdecl -D&lt;/em&gt;WIN32 -DWIN32 -DWIN32&lt;em&gt;LEAN&lt;/em&gt;AND&lt;em&gt;MEAN -DWNT -DBYPASS&lt;/em&gt;FLEX -D_INTEL=1 -DIPLIB=none -I. -I&quot;D:\src\include&quot; -I&quot;C:\Program Files\Microsoft Visual Studio&#xA;  9.0\VC\include&quot; -c -nologo -EHsc -W1 -Ox -Oy- -MD mymain.c&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The code compiles cleanly.  The link command is:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;link -debug -nologo -machine:IX86&#xA;  -verbose:lib -subsystem:console mymain.obj wsock32.lib advapi32.lib&#xA;  msvcrt.lib oldnames.lib kernel32.lib&#xA;  winmm.lib [snip large list of&#xA;  dependencies] D:\src\lib\app_main.obj&#xA;  -out:mymain.exe&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The errors that I'm getting are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;app&lt;em&gt;main.obj : error LNK2019:&#xA;  unresolved external symbol&#xA;  &quot;&lt;/em&gt;_declspec(dllimport) public: void&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;thiscall std::locale::facet::&lt;em&gt;Register(void)&quot;&#xA;  (&lt;/strong&gt;imp&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;em&gt;Register@facet@locale@std@@QAEXXZ)&#xA;  referenced in function &quot;class&#xA;  std::ctype const &amp;amp; _&lt;/em&gt;cdecl&#xA;  std::use&lt;em&gt;facet&#xA;  \&gt;(class std::locale const &amp;amp;)&quot; (??$use&lt;/em&gt;facet@V?$ctype@D@std@@@std@@YAABV?$ctype@D@0@ABVlocale@0@@Z)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;app&lt;em&gt;main.obj : error LNK2019:&#xA;  unresolved external symbol&#xA;  &quot;&lt;strong&gt;declspec(dllimport)  public: static&#xA;  unsigned int _&lt;/em&gt;cdecl&#xA;  std::ctype::&lt;em&gt;Getcat(class&#xA;  std::locale::facet const * *)&quot;&#xA;  (&lt;/strong&gt;imp&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;em&gt;Getcat@?$ctype@D@std@@SAIPAPBVfacet@locale@2@@Z)&#xA;  referenced in function &quot;class&#xA;  std::ctype const &amp;amp; _&lt;/em&gt;cdecl&#xA;  std::use&lt;em&gt;facet&#xA;  \&gt;(class std::locale const &amp;amp;)&quot; (??$use&lt;/em&gt;facet@V?$ctype@D@std@@@std@@YAABV?$ctype@D@0@ABVlocale@0@@Z)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;app&lt;em&gt;main.obj : error LNK2019:&#xA;  unresolved external symbol&#xA;  &quot;&lt;strong&gt;declspec(dllimport)  public: static&#xA;  unsigned int _&lt;/em&gt;cdecl&#xA;  std::ctype::&lt;em&gt;Getcat(class&#xA;  std::locale::facet const * *)&quot;&#xA;  (&lt;/strong&gt;imp&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;em&gt;Getcat@?$ctype@G@std@@SAIPAPBVfacet@locale@2@@Z)&#xA;  referenced in function &quot;class&#xA;  std::ctype const &amp;amp;&#xA;  _&lt;/em&gt;cdecl std::use&lt;em&gt;facet &gt;(class&#xA;  std::locale const &amp;amp;)&quot;&#xA;  (??$use&lt;/em&gt;facet@V?$ctype@G@std@@@std@@YAABV?$ctype@G@0@ABVlocale@0@@Z)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;mymain.exe : fatal error LNK1120: 3&#xA;  unresolved externals&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notice that these errors are coming from the legacy code, not my code - app_main.obj is part of the legacy code, while mymain.c is my source.  I've done some searching around, and what that I've read says that this type of error is caused by a mismatch with the -MD switch between my code and the library that I'm linking to.  Since I'm dealing with legacy code, a solution has to come from my environment. It's been a long time since I've done C++ work, and even longer since I've used Visual Studio, so I'm hoping that this is just some ignorance on my part.  Any ideas on how to get these resolved?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1322" OwnerDisplayName="Matt McMinn" LastActivityDate="2008-09-04T22:07:21.743" Title="C++ linker unresolved external symbols" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;" AnswerCount="4" />
<row Id="23210" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:04:34.940" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think the best thing to do here would be one/both of two things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rethink the design, if its too complex, find a less-complex way.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stop trying to visualise it.. :P Just store the dimensions in question that you need to sum, then do them one at a time. Once you have the base code, then look at improving the efficiency of your algorithm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:04:34.940" />
<row Id="23212" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23209" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:06:53.623" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;These are standard library references. Make sure that all libraries (including the standard library) are using the &lt;em&gt;same&lt;/em&gt; linkage. E.g. you can't link statically while linking the standard lib dynamically. The same goes for the threading model used. Take special care that you and the 3rd party library use the same linkage options.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This can be a real pain in the *ss.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:06:53.623" />
<row Id="23213" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23175" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:09:13.417" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;All you'll ever need to know (and then some):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee817645.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee817645.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and GC.Collect() forces a collect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastEditorUserId="55408" LastEditDate="2010-01-21T12:02:24.660" LastActivityDate="2010-01-21T12:02:24.660" />
<row Id="23214" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:10:28.467" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately there isnt really a simpler way to do this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="522" OwnerDisplayName="Ed" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:10:28.467" />
<row Id="23216" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23229" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:10:51.150" Score="3" ViewCount="801" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can never remember the differences in regular expression syntax used by tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grep&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;grep&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AWK&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;AWK&lt;/a&gt;, or languages like Python and PHP. Generally, Perl has the most expansive syntax, but I'm often hamstrung by the limitations of even &lt;code&gt;egrep&lt;/code&gt; (&quot;extended&quot; &lt;code&gt;grep&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there a site that lists the differences in a concise and easy-to-read fashion?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="726" OwnerDisplayName="yukondude" LastEditorUserId="63550" LastEditDate="2012-07-10T14:53:29.620" LastActivityDate="2012-07-10T14:53:29.620" Title="Summary of differences in regular expression syntax for various tools and languages?" Tags="&lt;regex&gt;&lt;grep&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
<row Id="23217" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23222" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:10:56.250" Score="13" ViewCount="1138" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been making a concerted effort to improve my javascript skills lately by reading as much javascript code as I can. In doing this I've sometimes seen the &lt;code&gt;javascript:&lt;/code&gt; prefix appended to the front of event handler attributes in HTML element tags. What's the purpose of this prefix? Basically, is there any appreciable difference between:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;onchange=&quot;javascript: myFunction(this)&quot;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;onchange=&quot;myFunction(this)&quot;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1680" OwnerDisplayName="Jesse" LastEditorUserId="146792" LastEditorDisplayName="Flubba" LastEditDate="2011-12-09T17:17:52.443" LastActivityDate="2011-12-09T17:17:52.443" Title="What's the purpose (if any) of &quot;javascript:&quot; in event handler tags?" Tags="&lt;javascript&gt;" AnswerCount="10" FavoriteCount="4" />
<row Id="23219" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23197" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:11:44.750" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is what I use to read from a Magtek card reader:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;//Open file on the device&#xA;deviceHandle = &#xA;    CreateFile (deviceDetail-&amp;gt;DevicePath, &#xA;    GENERIC_READ, FILE_SHARE_READ | FILE_SHARE_WRITE, &#xA;    NULL, OPEN_EXISTING, 0, NULL);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Try those options and see if you can at least read from the device.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I understand your pain here... I found the USB HID documentation to be basically wrong in several places.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[Edit] There's not much out there on this problem.  Here's a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.codeproject.com/KB/cs/USB_HID.aspx?fid=398968&amp;amp;df=90&amp;amp;mpp=25&amp;amp;noise=3&amp;amp;sort=Position&amp;amp;view=Quick&amp;amp;select=2657157&amp;amp;fr=26&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;codeproject link&lt;/a&gt; that lightly touches on the subject in a thread at the bottom.  Sounds like maybe if it's a keyboard or mouse windows grabs it exclusively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1219" OwnerDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastEditorUserId="1219" LastEditorDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T19:47:56.223" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:47:56.223" />
<row Id="23220" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23016" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:11:46.203" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Try and break your own site before someone else does. Your web site is basically a publicly accessible API that allows access to a database and other backend systems. Test the URLs as if they were any other API.  I like to start by cataloging all URLs that have some sort of permenant affect on the state of the system - this is easy if you are doing Ruby on Rails development or trying to follow a RESTful design pattern. For each of those URLs, try running a GET, POST, PUT or DELETE HTTP methods with different parameters so that you can ensure that you're only giving access to what you want to give access to. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This of course is in addition to obvious: Functional testing, Load Testing, SQL Injection, XSS etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1486" OwnerDisplayName="Kyle Boon" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:11:46.203" />
<row Id="23222" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:12:17.213" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;Probably nothing in your example. My understanding is that &quot;javascript:&quot; is for anchor tags (in place of an actual href). You'd use it so that your script can execute when the user clicks the link, but without initiating a navigation back to the page (which a blank href coupled with an onclick will do).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;javascript:someFunction();&quot;&amp;gt;Blah&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rather than:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;&quot; onclick=&quot;someFunction();&quot;&amp;gt;Blah&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1975282" OwnerDisplayName="DannySmurf" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:12:17.213" />
<row Id="23223" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23216" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:13:06.900" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I find this site helpful: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.regular-expressions.info/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.regular-expressions.info/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other than that, I use the corresponding documentation extensively and I believe, all said and done, there's no way around that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:13:06.900" />
<row Id="23224" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23178" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:13:09.210" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is this any use?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oops:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb774096&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb774096&lt;/a&gt;(VS.85).aspx&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2548" OwnerDisplayName="Remou" LastEditorUserId="2548" LastEditorDisplayName="Remou" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:03:48.167" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:03:48.167" />
<row Id="23225" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:13:10.347" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I beg to differ, there is ALWAYS another way..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you really &lt;em&gt;cannot&lt;/em&gt; refactor, then you need to break the problem down into smaller parts.. Like I said, establish which dimensions you need to sum, then hit them one at a time..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, stop changing the edits, they are correcting your spelling errors, they are trying to help you ;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:13:10.347" />
<row Id="23226" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:13:50.860" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;When you say you don't know how many dimensions there are, how exactly are you defining the data structures?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At some point, someone needs to create this array, and to do that, they need to know the dimensions of the array. You can force the creator to pass in this data along with the array.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unless the question is to define such a data structure...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1799" OwnerDisplayName="Mat Noguchi" LastEditorUserId="142162" LastEditDate="2012-07-03T15:02:20.720" LastActivityDate="2012-07-03T15:02:20.720" />
<row Id="23227" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23124" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:14:36.600" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;First off, I think you need to be clearer in your question - what technology are you using and where is this process that is timing out - server-side or client-side?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to have the server-side code take a long time and you are using .NET, place this line in the method you call server-side:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;System.Threading.Thread.Sleep(timeoutMilliseconds);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As long as you use a number sufficient so that your client-side code assumes the server has timed out, you should be good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1790" OwnerDisplayName="JasonBunting" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:14:36.600" />
<row Id="23228" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="24143" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:15:08.533" Score="33" ViewCount="2698" Body="&lt;p&gt;Compare&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String.Format(&quot;Hello {0}&quot;, &quot;World&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;with&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot;Hello {0}&quot;.Format(&quot;World&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why did the .Net designers choose a static method over an instance method? What do you think?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2361" OwnerDisplayName="Jakub Šturc" LastEditorUserId="234" LastEditorDisplayName="Orion Edwards" LastEditDate="2008-08-23T04:21:57.907" LastActivityDate="2012-07-03T14:54:51.347" Title="Why is String.Format static?" Tags="&lt;.net&gt;&lt;string&gt;&lt;design&gt;" AnswerCount="22" FavoriteCount="3" />
<row Id="23229" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23216" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:15:44.633" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0596528124&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Mastering Regular Expressions&lt;/a&gt;, devotes the last four chapters to Java, PHP, Perl, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/.NET_Framework&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;.NET&lt;/a&gt;.  One chapter for each. From what I know, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0596514271&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;pocket edition&lt;/a&gt; contains just those final four chapters.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastEditorUserId="63550" LastEditDate="2012-07-03T10:47:42.243" LastActivityDate="2012-07-03T10:47:42.243" />
<row Id="23232" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23216" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:16:14.117" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;For my own future reference, I'll offer the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.greenend.org.uk/rjk/2002/06/regexp.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Regexp Syntax Summary&lt;/a&gt; page which contrasts the syntax for &lt;code&gt;grep&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;egrep&lt;/code&gt;, Emacs, Perl, Python, and Tcl. As expected, Perl supports the greatest variety of operators, but Python looks equally capable, if not more so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="726" OwnerDisplayName="yukondude" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:16:14.117" />
<row Id="23234" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:17:18.920" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it's because it's a creator method (not sure if there's a better name). All it does is take what you give it and return a single string object. It doesn't operate on an existing object. If it was non-static, you would need a string to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:17:18.920" />
<row Id="23235" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16888" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:17:23.020" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Don't forget that the product backlog items should be rated in order of importance, using a weighting system (prime numbers, fibonacci,..), so that if you have items in your backlog that of similar importance (i.e. 2 items with a weight of 21), then they should in theory both try and be inserted in the sprint ahead of the 13s and 8s.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="178" OwnerDisplayName="steve_mtl" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:17:23.020" />
<row Id="23236" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:17:26.530" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Because the Format method has nothing to do with a string's current value. The value of the string isn't used. It takes a string and returns one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1627" OwnerDisplayName="Ryan Farley" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:17:26.530" />
<row Id="23237" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:17:53.583" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am no authority in JavaScript, and perhaps more of a dunce than the asker, but AFAIK, the difference is that the &quot;javascript:&quot; prefix is preferred/required in URI-contexts, where the argument may be as well a traditional HTTP URL as a JavaScript trigger.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, my intuitive answer would be that, since onChange expects JavaScript, the &quot;javascript:&quot; prefix is redundant (if not downright erroneous). You can, however, write &quot;javascript:myFunction(this)&quot; in your address bar, and that function is run. Without the &quot;javascript:&quot;, your browser would try to interpret &quot;myFunction(this)&quot; as a URL and tries to fetch the DNS info, browse to that server, etc...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2238" OwnerDisplayName="wolfie" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:17:53.583" />
<row Id="23239" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:18:22.240" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't know if the &quot;javascript:&quot; prefix means anything within the onevent attributes but I know they are annoying in anchor tags when trying to open the link in a new tab. The href should be used as a fall back and &lt;strong&gt;never&lt;/strong&gt; to attach javascript to links.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2118" OwnerDisplayName="Annan" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:18:22.240" />
<row Id="23240" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:19:10.443" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I see nothing wrong with it being static..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The semantics of the static method seem to make a lot more sense to me. Perhaps it is because it is a primitive. Where primitives are used to often, you want to make the utility code for working with them as light as possible.. Also, I think the semantics are a lot better with &lt;em&gt;String.Format&lt;/em&gt; over &lt;em&gt;&quot;MyString BLAH BLAH {0}&quot;.Format&lt;/em&gt; ...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:19:10.443" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23241" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5727" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:19:11.050" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that what makes pointers tricky to learn is that until pointers you're comfortable with the idea that &quot;at this memory location is a set of bits that represent an int, a double, a character, whatever&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you first see a pointer, you don't really get what's at that memory location. &quot;What do you mean, it holds an &lt;em&gt;address&lt;/em&gt;?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't agree with the notion that &quot;you either get them or you don't&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They become easier to understand when you start finding real uses for them (like not passing large structures into functions). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1179" OwnerDisplayName="Baltimark" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:19:11.050" CommunityOwnedDate="2010-01-13T14:01:00.703" />
<row Id="23242" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:19:31.800" Score="4" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;It should only be used in the href tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The accepted way is this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;/non-js-version/&quot; onclick=&quot;someFunction(); return false&quot;&amp;gt;Blah&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But to answer the OP, there is generally no reason to use &quot;javascript:&quot; anymore. In fact, you should attach the javascript event from your script, and not inline in the markup. But, that's a purist thing I think :-D&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1951" OwnerDisplayName="mercutio" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:19:31.800" />
<row Id="23243" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:19:32.330" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Instance methods are good when you have an object that maintains some state; the process of formatting a string does not affect the string you are operating on (read: does not modify its state), it creates a new string.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With extension methods, you can now have your cake and eat it too (i.e. you can use the latter syntax if it helps you sleep better at night).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1790" OwnerDisplayName="JasonBunting" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:19:32.330" />
<row Id="23244" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:20:02.500" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;It should not be used in event handlers (though most browsers work defensively, and will not punish you).  I would also argue that it should not be used in the href attribute of an anchor.  If a browser supports javascript, it will use the properly defined event handler.  If a browser does not, a javascript: link will appear broken.  IMO, it is better to point them to a page explaining that they need to enable javascript to use that functionality, or better yet a non-javascript required version of the functionality.  So, something like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;non-ajax.html&quot; onclick=&quot;niftyAjax(); return false;&quot;&amp;gt;Ajax me&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thought of a good reason to use javascript:.  Bookmarklets.  For instance, this one sends you to google reader to view the rss feeds for a page:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;var b=document.body;&#xA;if(b&amp;amp;&amp;amp;!document.xmlVersion){&#xA; void(z=document.createElement('script'));&#xA; void(z.src='http://www.google.com/reader/ui/subscribe-bookmarklet.js');&#xA;  void(b.appendChild(z));&#xA;}else{&#xA; location='http://www.google.com/reader/view/feed/'+encodeURIComponent(location.href)&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To have a user easily add this Bookmarklet, you would format it like so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;javascript:var%20b=document.body;if(b&amp;amp;&amp;amp;!document.xmlVersion){void(z=document.createElement('script'));void(z.src='http://www.google.com/reader/ui/subscribe-bookmarklet.js');void(b.appendChild(z));}else{location='http://www.google.com/reader/view/feed/'+encodeURIComponent(location.href)}&quot;&amp;gt;Drag this to your bookmarks, or right click and bookmark it!&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" OwnerDisplayName="Chris Marasti-Georg" LastEditorUserId="96" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Marasti-Georg" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T19:48:06.443" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:48:06.443" />
<row Id="23246" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23197" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:20:33.140" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Cool - I'll try those options, as they're probably better defaults given my intentions. Unfortunately, I know my device is there and I'll eventually need read/write access later on (once I inspect the descriptors and have verifed it is infact my device). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which means that my real goal IS to know what's using it, so I can inform the customer/user: &quot;Hey man, 'iexplore.exe' is currently using your SuperWidget device. You'll have to close that down in order to use SuperWidget application.&quot; (if not at the application-level, then at least at the phone support level.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I forgot to mention that the windows error reported by GetLastError() is:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;0x20. The process cannot access the file because it is being used by another process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(So your sharing alternatives will probably get the file open, assuming no FILE&lt;em&gt;SHARE&lt;/em&gt;NONE on behalf of the other process).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[edit]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Yeah, it's painful alright. I have seen mice and keyboards get locked by whatever Windows uses to read from them. I've also seen a lot of people have trouble inside a VM like Paralells on OS X, where the HID class driver has the device open exclusively preventing the VM from using standard USB requests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I've seen some code that recreates what &lt;em&gt;ProcessMonitor&lt;/em&gt; does. Maybe SysInternals is just electing to ignore device handles, but the same method (or a slight variation) can be employed here to determine the PID.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2146" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Haboustak" LastEditorUserId="2146" LastEditorDisplayName="Mike Haboustak" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:06:51.640" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:06:51.640" />
<row Id="23248" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:21:06.803" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I haven't tried it yet but you could make an extension method for what you want.  I wouldn't do it, but I think it would work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also I find &lt;code&gt;String.Format()&lt;/code&gt; more in line with other patterned static methods like &lt;code&gt;Int32.Parse()&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;long.TryParse()&lt;/code&gt;, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You cloud also just use a &lt;code&gt;StringBuilder&lt;/code&gt; if you want a non static format.&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/system.text.stringbuilder.appendformat&amp;#40;VS.85&amp;#41;.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;StringBuilder.AppendFormat()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1327" OwnerDisplayName="Dan" LastEditorUserId="234" LastEditorDisplayName="Orion Edwards" LastEditDate="2008-08-24T21:03:28.040" LastActivityDate="2008-08-24T21:03:28.040" />
<row Id="23250" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23502" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:21:25.227" Score="97" ViewCount="28510" Body="&lt;p&gt;This may be a silly question, but I was curious how other people use the &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt; keyword.  I tend to use it in constructors but may also use it throughout the class in other methods.  Some examples:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Constructor:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public Light(Vector v)&#xA;{&#xA;    this.dir = new Vector(v);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public void SomeMethod()&#xA;{&#xA;    Vector vec = new Vector();&#xA;    double d = (vec * vec) - (this.radius * this.radius);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2016" OwnerDisplayName="Magic Hat" LastEditorUserId="36565" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2012-12-07T16:58:55.503" LastActivityDate="2013-11-14T17:43:03.153" Title="When do you use the &quot;this&quot; keyword?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;coding-style&gt;" AnswerCount="34" FavoriteCount="34" ClosedDate="2011-08-30T20:39:27.283" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23253" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:22:23.663" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;String.Format&lt;/code&gt; takes at least one String and returns a different String. It doesn't need to modify the format string in order to return another string, so it makes little sense to do that (ignoring your formatting of it). On the other hand, it wouldn't be that much of a stretch to make &lt;code&gt;String.Format&lt;/code&gt; be a member function, except I don't think C# allows for const member functions like C++ does. [Please correct me and this post if it does.]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1799" OwnerDisplayName="Mat Noguchi" LastEditorUserId="142162" LastEditDate="2012-07-03T14:54:51.347" LastActivityDate="2012-07-03T14:54:51.347" />
<row Id="23255" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:22:32.103" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it looks better in general to use String.Format, but I could see a point in wanting to have a non-static function for when you already have a string stored in a variable that you want to &quot;format&quot;.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an aside, all functions of the string class don't act on the string, but return a new string object, because strings are immutable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:22:32.103" />
<row Id="23256" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:22:33.320" Score="37" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Because the Format method has nothing to do with a string's current value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's true for &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; string methods because .NET strings are immutable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If it was non-static, you would need a string to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It does: the format string.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe this is just another example of the many design flaws in the .NET platform (and I don't mean this as a flame; I still find the .NET framework superior to most other frameworks).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:22:33.320" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="23257" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:22:48.623" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;I use it every time I refer to an instance variable, even if I don't need to. I think it makes the code more clear.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:22:48.623" CommentCount="2" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23258" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:23:02.120" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I use it anywhere there might be ambiguity (obviously). Not just compiler ambiguity (it would be required in that case), but also ambiguity for someone looking at the code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1975282" OwnerDisplayName="DannySmurf" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:23:02.120" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23259" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:23:16.847" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I tend to underscore fields with _ so don't really ever need to use this. Also R# tends to refactor them away anyway...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1075" OwnerDisplayName="KiwiBastard" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:23:16.847" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23260" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:23:34.253" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;You should always use it, I use it to diferantiate private fields and parameters (because our naming conventions state that we don't use prefixes for member and parameter names (and they are based on information found on the internet, so I consider that a best practice))&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1782" OwnerDisplayName="Juan Manuel" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:23:34.253" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23264" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:26:06.900" Score="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;I only use it when absolutely necessary, ie, when another variable is shadowing another.  Such as here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;class Vector3&#xA;{&#xA;    float x;&#xA;    float y;&#xA;    float z;&#xA;&#xA;    public Vector3(float x, float y, float z)&#xA;    {&#xA;        this.x = x;&#xA;        this.y = y;&#xA;        this.z = z;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or as Ryan Fox points out, when you need to pass this as a parameter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1595" OwnerDisplayName="Corey" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:26:06.900" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23267" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:26:37.430" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;Any time you need a reference to the current object.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One particularly handy scenario is when your object is calling a function and wants to pass itself into it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;void onChange()&#xA;{&#xA;    screen.draw(this);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="55" OwnerDisplayName="Ryan Fox" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:26:37.430" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23268" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4689" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:26:55.150" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://dejavu.sourceforge.net/wiki/index.php/Main_Page&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;DejaVu&lt;/a&gt; Sans Mono (also known as Panic Sans), size 11, anti-alised. Previously I only used fonts that weren't anti-aliased, but it just seems to work for this font.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stuff.jeremybanks.ca/panicsans.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Panic Sans in TextMate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1114" OwnerDisplayName="Jeremy Banks" LastEditorUserId="1114" LastEditorDisplayName="Jeremy Banks" LastEditDate="2008-11-09T18:46:07.890" LastActivityDate="2008-11-09T18:46:07.890" CommunityOwnedDate="2008-09-19T22:36:21.473" />
<row Id="23269" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:27:18.007" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since there are a bunch of different functional programming languages, it's hard to recommend books. But if you're interested in Common Lisp, recently I've been reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/1590592395&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&quot;Practical Common Lisp&quot;&lt;/a&gt; by Peter Seibel, which you can &lt;a href=&quot;http://gigamonkeys.com/book/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;check out online for free&lt;/a&gt; before dropping your hard earned cash on it. It's a pretty gentle introduction to CL, with great explanations and tons of examples. Seibel's a great writer (example: read &lt;a href=&quot;http://gigamonkeys.com/book/macros-defining-your-own.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;the story of Mac&lt;/a&gt;,) he's good at keeping you engaged, which is really where SICP falls down, I think. It's just so dry! But while Practical Common Lisp is pretty example-heavy, it doesn't really have challenges to work through, although the examples are mostly designed to let you continue to work and build on them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another good book, this one Scheme-oriented: &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0262062186&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;How to Design Programs&lt;/a&gt;. (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.htdp.org/2003-09-26/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Online&lt;/a&gt;)&#xA;I haven't had as much time with this book, being more of a Lisper than a Schemer myself, but it's well written, has good explanations and examples, and has lots of exercises to work on. It seems pretty popular in the Scheme crowd.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="462356" OwnerDisplayName="JordanG" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:27:18.007" />
<row Id="23270" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="36667" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:28:00.140" Score="4" ViewCount="1217" Body="&lt;p&gt;Does anyone know how IE7 determines what Security Zone to use for a site?  I see the basics for IE6 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.microsoft.com/technet/prodtechnol/ie/reskit/6/default.mspx?mfr=true&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but I can't find the equivalent for IE7.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="466" OwnerDisplayName="qulup" LastEditorUserId="123" LastEditorDisplayName="Prakash" LastEditDate="2008-08-25T12:29:21.887" LastActivityDate="2008-12-03T17:30:02.460" Title="How IE7 determines a site's Security Zone" Tags="&lt;security&gt;&lt;internet-explorer-7&gt;&lt;security-zone&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="23271" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23016" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:28:03.323" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Turn off javascript and make sure your site can still be navigated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even if you want to ignore the small but significant number of people who have it disabled, this will impact search engines as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1990" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:28:03.323" />
<row Id="23272" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:28:42.010" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it says somewhere in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://twurl.nl/iafwwh&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;MS Coding Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; that generally you should always access via &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; ...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do on most occasions but sometimes when working on close-knit code like loops and stuff with lots of variable, I find it gets messy..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:28:42.010" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23273" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23166" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:28:49.187" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I learned from Jeffrey Ullman's &lt;em&gt;Elements of ML Programming&lt;/em&gt;, which is pretty good. It loses points for being about Standard ML, when OCaml, F#, and Haskell are (seemingly) more popular.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1412" OwnerDisplayName="Chris Conway" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:28:49.187" />
<row Id="23274" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16991" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:28:51.653" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NetBeans&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;NetBeans&lt;/a&gt; is good because you can use it on Windows and Mac OS X.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="453046" OwnerDisplayName="FortunateDuke" LastEditorUserId="63550" LastEditDate="2011-02-06T16:05:39.637" LastActivityDate="2011-02-06T16:05:39.637" CommentCount="3" CommunityOwnedDate="2011-04-26T15:17:02.180" />
<row Id="23275" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:29:03.460" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You're doing this in c/c++... so you have an array of array of array... you don't have to visualize 20 dimensions since that isn't how the data is laid out in memory, for a 2 dimensional:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[1] --&amp;gt; [1,2,3,4,5,6,...]&#xA;[2] --&amp;gt; [1,2,3,4,5,6,...]&#xA;[3] --&amp;gt; [1,2,3,4,5,6,...]&#xA;[4] --&amp;gt; [1,2,3,4,5,6,...]&#xA;[5] --&amp;gt; [1,2,3,4,5,6,...]&#xA; .           .&#xA; .           .&#xA; .           .&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so, why can't you iterate across the first one summing it's contents? If you are trying to find the size, then &lt;code&gt;sizeof(array)/sizeof(int)&lt;/code&gt; is a risky approach. You must know the dimension to be able to process this data, and set the memory up, so you know the depth of recursion to sum. Here is some pseudo code of what it seems you should do, &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sum( n_matrix, depth )&#xA;  running_total = 0&#xA;  if depth = 0 then&#xA;    foreach element in the array&#xA;      running_total += elm&#xA;  else &#xA;     foreach element in the array&#xA;       running_total += sum( elm , depth-1 )&#xA;  return running_total&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" OwnerDisplayName="nlucaroni" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:29:03.460" />
<row Id="23276" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23270" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:29:29.123" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Not sure what the confusion is. Sites on your intranet are in the intranet zone, web sites are in the internet zone, and sites on your computer are in the local zone, unless you've specifically overridden something in the browser's preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1975282" OwnerDisplayName="DannySmurf" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:29:29.123" />
<row Id="23277" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23290" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:29:45.253" Score="67" ViewCount="24884" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've read the Wikipedia articles for both &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Procedural_programming&quot;&gt;procedural programming&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Functional_programming&quot;&gt;functional programming&lt;/a&gt;, but I'm still slightly confused. Could someone boil it down to the core?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastEditorUserId="1693" LastEditorDisplayName="Steve M" LastEditDate="2008-08-25T11:41:13.653" LastActivityDate="2012-11-28T08:32:07.497" Title="What is the difference between procedural programming and functional programming?" Tags="&lt;functional-programming&gt;&lt;glossary&gt;&lt;programming-paradigms&gt;&lt;procedural-programming&gt;" AnswerCount="14" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="31" />
<row Id="23278" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:29:51.620" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I pretty much only use &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt; when referencing a type property from inside the same type.  As another user mentioned, I also underscore local fields so they are noticeable without needing &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1314" OwnerDisplayName="akmad" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:29:51.620" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23279" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:30:42.880" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;It depends on the coding standard I'm working under.  If we are using _ to denote an instance variable then &quot;this&quot; becomes redundant. If we are not using _ then I tend to use this to denote instance variable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1327" OwnerDisplayName="Dan" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:30:42.880" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23281" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:31:26.560" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I tend to use it everywhere as well, just to make sure that it is clear that it is instance members that we are dealing with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="920" OwnerDisplayName="Philippe" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:31:26.560" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23282" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:32:36.043" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;@Jeff&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I actually think this is an interesting question. I'm not sure how useful it is, but it is a valid question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;@Ed&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can you provide a little more info on this question? You said the dimension of the array is dynamic, but is the number of elements dynamic as well?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I'm going to try and answer the question anyways. I can't give you the code off the top of my head (it would take a while to get it right without any compiler here on this PC), but I can point you in the right direction ...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let's use 8 dimensions (0-7) with indexes 0 to 3 as an example. You care about only 1,2 and 6. This means you have two arrays. First, &lt;code&gt;array_care[4][4][4]&lt;/code&gt; for 1,2, and 6. The &lt;code&gt;array_care[4][4][4]&lt;/code&gt; will hold the end result.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, we want to iterate in a very specific way. We have the array &lt;code&gt;input[4][4][4][4][4][4][4][4]&lt;/code&gt; to parse through, and we care about dimensions 1, 2, and 6.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We need to define some temporary indexes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int dim[8] = {0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0};&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We also need to store the order in which we want to increase the indexes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int increase_index_order[8] = {7,5,4,3,0,6,2,1};&#xA;int i = 0;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This order is important for doing what you requested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Define a termination flag:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;bool terminate=false;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we can create our loop:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;while (terminate)&#xA;{&#xA;array_care[dim[1]][dim[2]][dim[6]] += input[dim[0]][dim[1]][dim[2]][dim[3]][dim[4]][dim[5]][dim[6]][dim[7]];&#xA;&#xA;while ((dim[increase_index_order[i]] = 3) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (i &amp;lt; 8))&#xA;{&#xA;dim[increase_index_order[i]]=0;&#xA;i++;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;if (i &amp;lt; 8) {&#xA;dim[increase_index_order[i]]++; i=0;&#xA;} else {&#xA;terminate=true;&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That should work for 8 dimensions, caring about 3 dimensions. It would take a bit more time to make it dynamic, and I don't have the time. Hope this helps. I apologize, but I haven't learned the code markups yet. :(&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1429" OwnerDisplayName="Marcus" LastEditorUserId="1429" LastEditorDisplayName="Marcus" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:32:24.120" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:32:24.120" />
<row Id="23285" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="21987" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:33:47.320" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Behaviour is the same when a window finishes flashing for as long as it's supposed to: the taskbar button stays coloured. I don't think this is a bug. If you think about it, when you use FLASHW_STOP, the flashing does in fact stop, but the point of the flashing is to get the user's attention. The button stays coloured because the user still may not have looked down and discovered &lt;em&gt;which&lt;/em&gt; window was trying to get her attention. Keeping the button coloured keeps that information available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1975282" OwnerDisplayName="DannySmurf" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:33:47.320" />
<row Id="23286" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23277" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:34:42.480" Score="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;In computer science, functional programming is a programming paradigm that treats computation as the evaluation of mathematical functions and avoids state and mutable data. It emphasizes the application of functions, in contrast with the procedural programming style that emphasizes changes in state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1782" OwnerDisplayName="Juan Manuel" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:34:42.480" />
<row Id="23287" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="242189" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:35:50.513" Score="49" ViewCount="44057" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the best approach to calculating the largest prime factor of a number?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm thinking the most efficient would be the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Find lowest prime number that divides cleanly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check if result of division is prime&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If not, find next lowest&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to 2.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm basing this assumption on it being easier to calculate the small prime factors. Is this about right? What other approaches should I look into?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: I've now realised that my approach is futile if there are more than 2 prime factors in play, since step 2 fails when the result is a product of two other primes, therefore a recursive algorithm is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit again: And now I've realised that this does still work, because the last found prime number has to be the highest one, therefore any further testing of the non-prime result from step 2 would result in a smaller prime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1951" OwnerDisplayName="mercutio" LastEditorUserId="1416970" LastEditorDisplayName="Alexander Prokofyev" LastEditDate="2012-10-06T05:07:10.693" LastActivityDate="2013-12-12T22:07:13.917" Title="Prime factors" Tags="&lt;algorithm&gt;&lt;math&gt;&lt;primes&gt;&lt;factors&gt;" AnswerCount="14" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="36" />
<row Id="23288" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23292" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:36:06.033" Score="23" ViewCount="70477" Body="&lt;p&gt;Where can I get some decent looking free ASP.Net or CSS themes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1287" OwnerDisplayName="vitule" LastEditorUserId="305" LastEditorDisplayName="Mark Biek" LastEditDate="2008-09-02T19:18:18.530" LastActivityDate="2013-03-07T18:42:47.013" Title="Free ASP.Net and/or CSS Themes" Tags="&lt;asp.net&gt;&lt;css&gt;&lt;themes&gt;&lt;free&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="24" ClosedDate="2012-08-02T16:06:17.433" />
<row Id="23290" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23277" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:37:53.580" Score="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;A functional language (ideally) allows you to write a mathematical function, i.e. a function that takes &lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; arguments and returns a value. If the program is executed, this function is evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A procedural language, on the other hand, performs a series of &lt;em&gt;sequential&lt;/em&gt; steps, where the functional program would be nested. There's a way of transforming sequential logic into functional logic called &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continuation_passing_style&quot;&gt;continuation passing style&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a consequence, a purely functional program always yields &lt;em&gt;the same value&lt;/em&gt; for an input, and the order of evaluation is not well-defined; which means that uncertain values like user input or random values are hard to model in purely functional languages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:37:53.580" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="23292" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23288" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:39:11.143" Score="21" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wouldn't bother looking for ASP.NET stuff specifically (probably won't find any anyways). Finding a good CSS theme easily can be used in ASP.NET.   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's some sites that I love for CSS goodness:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.freecsstemplates.org/&quot;&gt;http://www.freecsstemplates.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.oswd.org/&quot;&gt;http://www.oswd.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.openwebdesign.org/&quot;&gt;http://www.openwebdesign.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.styleshout.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.styleshout.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.freelayouts.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.freelayouts.com/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1627" OwnerDisplayName="Ryan Farley" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:39:11.143" />
<row Id="23294" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23288" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:39:56.073" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.oswd.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Open source Web Design&lt;/a&gt; in the past.  They have quite a few css themes, don't know about ASP.Net&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2328" OwnerDisplayName="Craig H" LastEditorUserId="437301" LastEditDate="2013-03-07T18:42:47.013" LastActivityDate="2013-03-07T18:42:47.013" />
<row Id="23295" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22697" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:42:40.060" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;We are heavily using &lt;a href=&quot;http://easymock.org&quot;&gt;EasyMock&lt;/a&gt; and EasyMock Class Extension at work and are pretty happy with it. It basically gives you everything you need. Take a look at the documentation, there's a very nice example which shows you all the features of EasyMock.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" OwnerDisplayName="david" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:42:40.060" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="23297" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23175" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:44:11.367" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;While I obviously cannot speak to the specifics of your application, in most instances you should not tie your caching implementation to some perceived expectation for how the GC will work.  As Stu mentions, calling GC.Collect() will force a collection (with overloads for a specific generation) but more often than not doing so will result in worse performance than just letting the GC manage itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you do find (after doing some real performance testing) that you need to interact with the GC make sure you take into account the different types of GC's that the framework currently has (see &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.msdn.com/maoni/archive/2004/09/25/234273.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for more information).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1314" OwnerDisplayName="akmad" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:44:11.367" />
<row Id="23300" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23106" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:45:47.540" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would use &lt;a href=&quot;http://jcp.org/en/jsr/detail?id=173&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Stax&lt;/a&gt; to parse XML, it's fast and easy to use. I've been using it on my last project to parse XML files up to 24MB. There's a nice introduction on &lt;a href=&quot;http://today.java.net/pub/a/today/2006/07/20/introduction-to-stax.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;java.net&lt;/a&gt;, which tells you everything you need to know to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" OwnerDisplayName="david" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:45:47.540" />
<row Id="23306" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:46:46.383" Score="21" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can't believe all of the people that say using it always is a &quot;best practice&quot; and such.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use &quot;this&quot; when there is ambiguity, as in &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/a/23264/282110&quot;&gt;Corey's example&lt;/a&gt; or when you need to pass the object as a parameter, as in &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/a/23267/282110&quot;&gt;Ryan's example&lt;/a&gt;. There is no reason to use it otherwise because being able to resolve a variable based on the scope chain should be clear enough that qualifying variables with it should be unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: The C# documentation on &quot;this&quot; indicates one more use, besides the two I mentioned, for the &quot;this&quot; keyword - &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/dk1507sz%28VS.71%29.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;for declaring indexers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: @Juan: Huh, I don't see any inconsistency in my statements - there are 3 instances when I would use the &quot;this&quot; keyword (as documented in the C# documentation), and those are times when you actually &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; it. Sticking &quot;this&quot; in front of variables in a constructor when there is no shadowing going on is simply a waste of keystrokes and a waste of my time when reading it, it provides no benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1790" OwnerDisplayName="JasonBunting" LastEditorUserId="282110" LastEditorDisplayName="JasonBunting" LastEditDate="2012-04-25T20:09:38.907" LastActivityDate="2012-04-25T20:09:38.907" CommentCount="1" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23307" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:46:57.863" Score="0" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;x = number_of_dimensions;&#xA;while (x &amp;gt; 1)&#xA;{&#xA;  switch (x)&#xA;  {&#xA;    case 20:&#xA;      reduce20DimensionArray();&#xA;      x--;&#xA;    break;&#xA;    case 19:&#xA;      .....&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Sorry, couldn't resist.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="517" OwnerDisplayName="Adam V" LastEditorUserId="517" LastEditorDisplayName="Adam V" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:13:51.700" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:13:51.700" />
<row Id="23308" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18533" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:47:15.790" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been using the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Data_Transfer_Object&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Data Transfer Objects&lt;/a&gt; pattern (originally from the Java world, I believe), with a SqDataReader to populate collections of DTOs from the data layer for use in other layers of the application.&#xA;The DTOs themselves are very lightweight and simple classes composed of properties with gets/sets. They can be easily serialized/deserialized, and used for databinding, making them pretty well suited to most of my development needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1680" OwnerDisplayName="Jesse" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:47:15.790" />
<row Id="23310" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23353" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:49:05.457" Score="5" ViewCount="1917" Body="&lt;p&gt;What would be the best version control system to learn as a beginner to source control?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="453046" OwnerDisplayName="FortunateDuke" LastEditorUserId="5058" LastEditorDisplayName="Bobby Jack" LastEditDate="2008-10-10T19:04:26.893" LastActivityDate="2011-04-12T08:17:48.870" Title="Source Control Beginners" Tags="&lt;version-control&gt;" AnswerCount="16" FavoriteCount="6" />
<row Id="23312" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23288" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:49:46.437" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;As always, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.csszengarden.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.csszengarden.com/&lt;/a&gt;. Note that the images aren't public domain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:49:46.437" />
<row Id="23314" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:50:14.067" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anything, but I would learn a modern system like git or subversion myself. My first VCS was RCS, but I got the basics down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:50:14.067" />
<row Id="23316" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:51:03.440" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, if you are just wanting to learn on your own, I would say you should go with something free, like subversion.  If you are a company who has never used source control before, then it really depends on your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2328" OwnerDisplayName="Craig H" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:51:03.440" />
<row Id="23319" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23634" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:51:54.857" Score="6" ViewCount="546" Body="&lt;p&gt;After reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffeeghost.net/2008/08/22/bugging-your-code-reviews/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;, I'm thinking that it might be a good idea...occasionally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;the neurotic paranoid in me began to wonder how close of an eye they were putting on my code. Especially after a few times where I noticed bugs right before I checked in the supposedly reviewed code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;p&gt;So I came up the concept of Jester bugs. Jester is a unit test tester for Java. It works by making a syntactically correct change to the original source code under test, compiling it, and then running the unit test suite. If the unit test suite results in everything being A-okay, then you know that the test suite is flawed because it missed the monkey wrench that was thrown into the code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Jester bugs are bugs that you intentionally introduce into your code, to see if your code reviewer is really spotting bugs in your code or just giving it a pass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-- Al Sweigart&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditorDisplayName="Flubba" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:07:24.570" LastActivityDate="2011-08-13T17:23:39.213" Title="Should you bug the code used in code reviews?" Tags="&lt;code-review&gt;" AnswerCount="17" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="23321" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:53:08.567" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd suggest you try Subversion, for example with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://svn1clicksetup.tigris.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;1-click SVN installer&lt;/a&gt;. Try searching SO for &quot;Subversion&quot;, and you'll find loads of questions with answers that point to good tutorials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1037" OwnerDisplayName="onnodb" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:53:08.567" />
<row Id="23322" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:53:17.523" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;My first exposure was CVS with WinCVS as a client.  it was horrid.  Next was Subversion, with TortoiseSVN and Eclipse's integration.  It was intuitive, and heavenly.  I think that using CVS with TortoiseCVS and Eclipse's would be nice as well, though I prefer the way SVN handles revisioning. The entire repository is versioned with each check in, not individual files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" OwnerDisplayName="Chris Marasti-Georg" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:53:17.523" />
<row Id="23323" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:53:31.173" Score="-6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Never. Ever. If you have variable shadowing, your naming conventions are on crack. I mean, really, no distinguishing naming for member variables? &lt;em&gt;Facepalm&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:53:31.173" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23324" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23277" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:53:55.163" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;To expand on Konrad's comment:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;As a consequence, a purely functional program always yields the same value for an input, and the order of evaluation is not well-defined;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because of this, functional code is generally easier to parallelize.  Since there are (generally) no side effects of the functions, and they (generally) just act on their arguments, a lot of concurrency issues go away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Functional programming is also used when you need to be capable of &lt;em&gt;proving&lt;/em&gt; your code is correct.  This is much harder to do with procedural programming (not easy with functional, but still easier).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer:  I haven't used functional programming in years, and only recently started looking at it again, so I might not be completely correct here. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1409" OwnerDisplayName="Herms" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:53:55.163" />
<row Id="23327" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:56:00.980" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;No.  Emailing a few hundred or thousand lines of code to somebody and saying &quot;Please review this&quot; is never going to result in a thorough review.  If you think people aren't reviewing the code when you do this, you're right.  Intentionally putting bugs into the code is just turning this ridiculous practice into a game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only way to properly review code is to get people together and go through it together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1175" OwnerDisplayName="Kristopher Johnson" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:56:00.980" />
<row Id="23328" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:56:08.747" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, I know that if I ever did this, I would forget it and thus purposefully introduce a bug into the codebase. So, I'm not sure this is a good idea unless you've got a good memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:56:08.747" />
<row Id="23329" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:56:09.997" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are a few core concepts that I think are important to learn:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check-ins/check-outs (obviously)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local versions vs. server versions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mapping/Binding a local workspace to a remote store or repository.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Merging your changes back into a file that contains changes from&#xA;others.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Branching (what it is, when/why to use it)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Merging changes from a branch back into a main branch or trunk.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most modern source control systems require some knowledge of the above topics and should help facilitate you learning them. Then you have distributed source control, which I don't have any experience with but is supposed to be fairly complicated and may not be suitable for a beginner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://subversion.tigris.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Subversion&lt;/a&gt; is great because it has all of the modern features you'd want and is free.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://git-scm.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; is also becoming an increasingly popular option and is another free or very low cost alternative to Subversion. Knowledge regarding the concepts of branching and merging become critical for using Git, however.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;a href=&quot;http://unfuddle.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;unfuddle&lt;/a&gt; as a free and easy way to experiment with both Git and Subversion. I use it to host a couple of subversion repositories for some side projects I've worked on in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1680" OwnerDisplayName="Jesse" LastEditorUserId="1680" LastEditDate="2009-12-04T20:28:31.047" LastActivityDate="2009-12-04T20:28:31.047" />
<row Id="23330" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:56:28.433" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wanna say &quot;Are you serious?&quot; but I can kinda see your point...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I probably would not do this though, but rather actually wave the code in their face and ask for actual answers and get them to engage their brain... Maybe even plant one to get their attention there and then, maybe they will then feel more compelled to review it properly after check in...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wouldn't like to check in bugs on purpose, just out of fear of me losing track of where the bug is ^_^&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastEditorUserId="496830" LastEditDate="2011-03-15T21:59:21.080" LastActivityDate="2011-03-15T21:59:21.080" />
<row Id="23331" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:56:43.427" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's something I've done before when discussing rules for an online game, we'd add in silly things so that we'd know that each of us were actually reading the suggestions. It was all good humoured and very helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1384652" OwnerDisplayName="Teifion" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:56:43.427" />
<row Id="23333" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23287" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:57:15.860" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it would be good to store somewhere all possible primes smaller then n and just iterate through them to find the biggest divisior. You can get primes from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prime-numbers.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;prime-numbers.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course I assume that your number isn't too big :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1516" OwnerDisplayName="Klesk" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:57:15.860" />
<row Id="23334" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:57:17.107" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;something about intentionally adding bugs to your code to catch your co-workers just doesn't sit right with me.  I say you just do &lt;a href=&quot;http://satc.gsfc.nasa.gov/Documents/fi/gdb/fitext.txt&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Formal Inspections&lt;/a&gt;.  Then you know your code was reviewed, plus they have been shown to find more bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2328" OwnerDisplayName="Craig H" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:57:17.107" />
<row Id="23335" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23277" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:57:34.877" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe that procedural/functional/objective programming are about how to approach a problem. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first style would plan everything in to steps, and solves the problem by implementing one step (a procedure) at a time. On the other hand, functional programming would emphasize the divide-and-conquer approach, where the problem is divided into sub-problem, then each sub-problem is solved (creating a function to solve that sub problem) and the results are combined to create the answer for the whole problem. Lastly, Objective programming would mimic the real world by create a mini-world inside the computer with many objects, each of which has a (somewhat) unique characteristics, and interacts with others. From those interactions the result would emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each style of programming has its own advantages and weaknesses. Hence, doing something such as &quot;pure programming&quot; (i.e. purely procedural - no one does this, by the way, which is kind of weird - or purely functional or purely objective) is very difficult, if not impossible, except some elementary problems specially designed to demonstrate the advantage of a programming style (hence, we call those who like pureness &quot;weenie&quot; :D).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, from those styles, we have programming languages that is designed to optimized for some each style. For example, Assembly is all about procedural. Okay, most early languages are procedural, not only Asm, like C, Pascal, (and Fortran, I heard). Then, we have all famous Java in objective school (Actually, Java and C# is also in a class called &quot;money-oriented,&quot; but that is subject for another discussion). Also objective is Smalltalk. In functional school, we would have &quot;nearly functional&quot; (some considered them to be impure) Lisp family and  ML family and many &quot;purely functional&quot; Haskell, Erlang, etc. By the way, there are many general languages such as Perl, Python, Ruby.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hope I have answered your question (and you are still awake).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="Lam Luu" LastEditorUserId="31615" LastEditorDisplayName="Harleqin" LastEditDate="2009-02-16T14:09:10.657" LastActivityDate="2009-02-16T14:09:10.657" />
<row Id="23336" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:57:48.993" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't agree with the way the blogger is doing it. Code reviews should be done in person, in a room, with everyone there. But the idea of putting a bug in the code still stands, to see if people (1) read the code before they came to the meeting and (2) are paying attention and thinking during the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" OwnerDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:57:48.993" />
<row Id="23339" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="20910" CreationDate="2008-08-22T19:59:58.833" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Silverlight programmer's don't know what they're missing out on, when it comes to Flex.  Silverlight lacks the component model and event triggering capabilites that Flex has.  Using XNA, and C#, a friend of mine has to jump through all kinds of hoops to get his Silverlight application to work.  Then, it has to be handed off to a designer to get it to look half way decent.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Listen to the deepfriedbytes.com podcasts on Silverlight, and you'll hear how even a couple guys that really push Silverlight, acknowledge some of these issues.  (I &lt;em&gt;think&lt;/em&gt;, if I recall correctly, one of the guys works for Microsoft, but I could be wrong - I listened to it last week).  They agree that Silverlight isn't quite ready for any huge applications, in its current state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would go with Flex, for a nice clean, straightforward approach - especially if you're already familiar with Flash and ActionScript 3.0.  Flex makes alot more sense, in my opinion - Silverlight still has to mature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1935" OwnerDisplayName="JasonMichael" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T19:59:58.833" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23340" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:00:47.333" Score="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;I use it whenever &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.msdn.microsoft.com/sourceanalysis&quot;&gt;StyleCop&lt;/a&gt; tells me to. &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.msdn.microsoft.com/sourceanalysis&quot;&gt;StyleCop&lt;/a&gt; must be obeyed. Oh yes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2084" OwnerDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:00:47.333" CommentCount="2" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23342" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:01:21.747" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;javascript: in JS code (like in an onclick attribute) is just a label for use with continue/goto label statements that may or may not be supported by the browser (probably not anywhere). It could be zipzambam: instead. Even if the label can't be used, browsers still accept it so it doesn't cause an error.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This means that if someone's throwing a useless label in an onclick attribute, they probably don't know what they're doing and are just copying and pasting or doing it out of habit from doing the below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;javascript: in the href attribute signifies a Javascript URI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://shadow2531.com/js/jsuri.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Example&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;javascript:(function()%7Balert(%22test%22)%3B%7D)()%3B&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1697" OwnerDisplayName="Shadow2531" LastEditorUserId="1697" LastEditorDisplayName="Shadow2531" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T20:37:51.300" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:37:51.300" />
<row Id="23344" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23319" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:01:59.390" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I remember seeing someone once suggest that you should not compile your code before a code review, and then try to find compile errors at the review.  The theory was, once the review was over, you can actually compile the code and see how many compile errors you didn't find in the review.  It is then safe to say that you missed that many logic errors as well.  Don't know if I could ever force myself to not type &quot;make&quot; but it did make me think, and it would help with this problem as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2328" OwnerDisplayName="Craig H" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:01:59.390" />
<row Id="23348" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:02:37.220" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;String.Format has to be a static method because strings are immutable.&lt;/strong&gt; Making it an instance method would imply you could use it to &quot;format&quot; or modify the value of an existing string. This you can't do, and making it an instance method that returned a new string would make no sense. Hence, it's a static method.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2189331" OwnerDisplayName="CodingTheWheel" LastEditorUserId="2189331" LastEditDate="2010-02-23T17:20:56.927" LastActivityDate="2010-02-23T17:20:56.927" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="23353" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:09:20.993" Score="23" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anything but Visual Source Safe; preferably one which supports the concepts of branching and merging. As others have said, Subversion is a great choice, especially with the TortoiseSVN client.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check out (pardon the pun) &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ericsink.com/scm/source_control.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Eric Sink's classic series of Source Control HOWTO articles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2084" OwnerDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:09:20.993" CommentCount="5" />
<row Id="23359" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="888" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:10:54.860" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;The integrated debuggers where you can watch the values of variable change as you step through code are really cool. They do, however, require software setup on the server and a certain amount of configuration on the client. Both of which require periodic maintenance to keep in good working order.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A print_r is easy to write and is guaranteed to work in any setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2158" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:10:54.860" CommunityOwnedDate="2011-03-09T11:34:12.603" />
<row Id="23365" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:13:33.043" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23217/whats-the-purpose-if-any-of-javascript-in-event-handler-tags#23242&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;@mercutio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;That's ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No, it's not ridiculous, javascript: is a pseudo protocol that can indeed only be used as the subject of a link, so he's quite right. Your suggestion is indeed better, but the best way of all is to use unobtrusive javascript techniques to iterate over HTML elements and add behaviour programmatically, as used in libraries like jQuery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" OwnerDisplayName="Flubba" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:13:33.043" />
<row Id="23367" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23205" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:14:35.333" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You definitely want to test physically pulling the cable out.  Lots of networking code will throw different exceptions in that scenario vs when the connection has just been lost.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2348" OwnerDisplayName="TimK" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:14:35.333" />
<row Id="23368" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23205" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:16:01.647" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;To add to TimK's answer, if you have a router, test pulling the upstream link on the router, this will test a bad connection without your system knowing that you lost the physical link.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="163" OwnerDisplayName="thelsdj" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:16:01.647" />
<row Id="23370" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:16:42.363" Score="1" ViewCount="570" Body="&lt;p&gt;My C# program has a list of files that can be dragged from it and dropped into another program. My requirements are that the file be copied to a different directory first.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, can I be notified of the drop operation so that I can only copy the file if operation succeeds? I'd rather wait till I know it needs to be copied before actually performing the copy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, is it possible to know what program the drop operation is occurring in? Ideally I'd like to alter the filepath based on who or what its being dropped.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The solution to this can be in any .NET language or C/C++ with COM.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="645" OwnerDisplayName="Joel Lucsy" LastEditorUserId="6899" LastEditorDisplayName="ΤΖΩΤΖΙΟΥ" LastEditDate="2008-10-23T01:59:44.787" LastActivityDate="2008-10-23T01:59:44.787" Title="Notification of drop in drag-drop in Windows" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;c++&gt;&lt;windows&gt;&lt;winapi&gt;&lt;com&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
<row Id="23371" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:16:57.683" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I understand correctly, you want to sum all values in the cross section defined at each &quot;bin&quot; along 1 dimension.  I suggest making a 1D array for your destination, then looping through each element in your array adding the value to the destination with the index of the dimension of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are using arbitrary number of dimensions, you must have a way of addressing elements (I would be curious how you are implementing this).  Your implementation of this will affect how you set the destination index.  But an obvious way would be with if statements checked in the iteration loops.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1807" OwnerDisplayName="dmo" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:16:57.683" />
<row Id="23372" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:17:27.683" Score="0" ViewCount="4127" Body="&lt;p&gt;What would be the best method for getting a custom element (that is using J2ME native Graphics) painted on LWUIT elements?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The custom element is an implementation from mapping library, that paints it's content (for example Google map) to Graphics object. How would it be possible to paint the result directly on LWUIT elements (at the moment I am trying to paint it on a Component). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is the only way to write a wrapper in LWUIT package, that would expose the internal implementation of it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;John:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; your solution looks like a lot of engineering :P What I ended up using is following wrapper:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;package com.sun.lwuit;&#xA;&#xA;public class ImageWrapper {&#xA;  private final Image image;&#xA;&#xA;  public ImageWrapper(final Image lwuitBuffer) {&#xA;    this.image = lwuitBuffer;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  public javax.microedition.lcdui.Graphics getGraphics() {&#xA;    return image.getGraphics().getGraphics();&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I can get the 'native' Graphics element from LWUIT. Paint on it - effectively painting on LWUIT image. And I can use the image to paint on a component.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it still looks like a hack :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But the real problem is 50kB of code overhead, even after obfuscation. But this is a issue for another post :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;/JaanusSiim&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="706" OwnerDisplayName="JaanusSiim" LastEditorUserId="706" LastEditorDisplayName="JaanusSiim" LastEditDate="2008-09-08T17:20:15.487" LastActivityDate="2008-09-17T18:45:20.260" Title="Painting javax.microedition.lcdui.Graphics on LWUIT Component" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;java-me&gt;&lt;lwuit&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
<row Id="23373" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23406" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:18:12.610" Score="8" ViewCount="12557" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a simple little test app written in Flex 3 (MXML and some AS3).  I can compile it to a SWF just fine, but I'd like to make it into an EXE so I can give it to a couple of my coworkers who might find it useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Flash 8, I could just target an EXE instead of a SWF and it would wrap the SWF in a projector, and everything worked fine.  Is there an equivalent to that using the Flex 3 SDK that doesn't end up requiring AIR?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note:  I don't have Flex Builder, I'm just using the free Flex 3 SDK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1409" OwnerDisplayName="Herms" LastActivityDate="2011-04-20T11:51:40.417" Title="Create an EXE from a SWF using Flex 3 without requiring AIR?" Tags="&lt;flex&gt;&lt;flash&gt;&lt;actionscript-3&gt;&lt;swf&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="5" />
<row Id="23375" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23555" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:20:50.653" Score="6" ViewCount="3666" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is anyone programming in Visual Foxpro out there?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm stuck supporting a legacy foxpro system. Wanted to know who else is out there is using Foxpro.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Added 9/11/2008: Thanks to all of you who responded!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="479" OwnerDisplayName="Christopher Mahan" LastEditorUserId="479" LastEditorDisplayName="Christopher Mahan" LastEditDate="2008-09-12T06:36:05.173" LastActivityDate="2013-10-29T15:04:17.323" Title="Anyone programming in Visual Foxpro out there?" Tags="&lt;foxpro&gt;" AnswerCount="19" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2011-09-25T05:35:19.320" />
<row Id="23376" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:21:39.717" Score="0" ViewCount="1371" Body="&lt;p&gt;Has anyone found a good compression format for MS Sqlserver databases? If so, what do you use and are you pleased with how it performs? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My company frequently will compress a database snapshot from one of our clients and download it so we have a local copy for testing and dev purposes. We tried zip in the past, but once the database files crossed the 4Gb boundary we had to use rar (zip is 32-bit only). The problem is rar takes a lot of time to compress, and we don't know if it gives us the best compression ratio either.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn't a question about the compression utility so much as the compression format. We use WinRar, but are considering 7zip, which supports a number of formats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2188" OwnerDisplayName="Magus" LastEditorUserId="15401" LastEditorDisplayName="Nigel Campbell" LastEditDate="2008-10-08T22:35:13.987" LastActivityDate="2008-10-08T22:39:31.607" Title="Best/fastest compression format for (sqlserver) databases?" Tags="&lt;sql-server&gt;&lt;compression&gt;&lt;zip&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
<row Id="23382" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23441" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:22:47.420" Score="4" ViewCount="4499" Body="&lt;p&gt;What are the different approaches for creating scheduled tasks for web applications, with or without a separate web/desktop application?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2141" OwnerDisplayName="Krishna Kumar" LastEditorUserId="68304" LastEditorDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastEditDate="2012-05-04T05:41:50.880" LastActivityDate="2012-05-04T05:41:50.880" Title="Scheduled Tasks for Web Applications" Tags="&lt;scheduled-tasks&gt;" AnswerCount="11" />
<row Id="23385" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23277" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:23:21.117" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;To expand on Konrad's comment:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;and the order of evaluation is not&#xA;  well-defined&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some functional languages have what is called Lazy Evaluation.  Which means a function is not executed until the value is needed.  Until that time the function itself is what is passed around.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Procedural languages are step 1 step 2 step 3... if in step 2 you say add 2 + 2, it does it right then.  In lazy evaluation you would say add 2 + 2, but if the result is never used, it never does the addition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="580" OwnerDisplayName="Brian Leahy" LastEditorUserId="31615" LastEditorDisplayName="Harleqin" LastEditDate="2009-02-16T14:10:18.767" LastActivityDate="2009-02-16T14:10:18.767" />
<row Id="23386" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:24:12.610" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think Stack Overflow itself is using an ApplicationCache expiration to run background code at intervals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1219" OwnerDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:24:12.610" />
<row Id="23387" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:24:55.637" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're on a Linux host, you'll almost certainly be using &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cron&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;cron&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1902010" OwnerDisplayName="ceejayoz" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:24:55.637" />
<row Id="23388" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23440" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:25:03.310" Score="9" ViewCount="1114" Body="&lt;p&gt;Your project manager says you must fix this bug, and asks you how long it will take.&#xA;You spend some time tracing through your code, and inspecting it for defects, and don't manage to nail down any causes. Your project manager insists on a number from you, and won't take unknown for an answer.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So what would you have said?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2430" OwnerDisplayName="Keshi" LastEditorUserId="1584286" LastEditDate="2013-07-05T08:55:56.657" LastActivityDate="2013-07-05T08:55:56.657" Title="What do you do when you have to give a time estimate on fixing a bug, when initial investigation/debugging proves inconclusive?" Tags="&lt;estimation&gt;" AnswerCount="13" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2013-07-05T12:20:07.707" />
<row Id="23389" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23376" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:25:19.613" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;In sql 2008 you have native compression, if you have to do this a lot and don't have SQL server 2008 then take a look at something like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.quest.com/litespeed-for-sql-server/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Quest LiteSpeed&lt;/a&gt; which compreeses the backup automatically&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="740" OwnerDisplayName="SQLMenace" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:25:19.613" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23391" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23505" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:25:46.103" Score="7" ViewCount="721" Body="&lt;p&gt;My path to a 'fulltime'- developer stated as a analyst using VBA with Excel, Access, and then onto C#.  I went to college part time once I discovered I had a passion for coding not business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do about most of my coding in C#, but being an ASP.NET developer I also write in HTML, JavaScript, SQL etc. . .  the usual suspects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I like to keep moving forward find the edge that will get me to the next level, the next job, and of course more money.  Most importantly I just want to learning something new and challenge me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have spent time recently learning LINQ, but was wondering what should I learn next?  Something on the .NET Framework or a new language technology?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2469" OwnerDisplayName="Longhorn213" LastEditorUserId="168868" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2012-07-07T07:42:46.113" LastActivityDate="2013-08-01T16:51:38.383" Title="Increases Skills what should I learn?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;.net&gt;" AnswerCount="10" FavoriteCount="6" />
<row Id="23392" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:26:04.587" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Under linux you can use cron jobs (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.unixgeeks.org/security/newbie/unix/cron-1.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.unixgeeks.org/security/newbie/unix/cron-1.html&lt;/a&gt;) to schedule tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use URL fetchers like wget or curl to make HTTP GET requests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Secure your URLs with authentication so that no one can execute the tasks without knowing the user/password.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2554" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:26:04.587" />
<row Id="23393" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:26:08.473" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd also recommend Subversion. It does not take too long to set up, it is free, and there is a really good book available online that goes over the basics as well as some advanced topics: &lt;a href=&quot;http://svnbook.red-bean.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://svnbook.red-bean.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1441" OwnerDisplayName="crashmstr" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:26:08.473" />
<row Id="23394" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:26:22.623" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you just have to say, &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&quot;I can't give you an exact time frame yet.  Let me keep investigating and I'll let you know as soon as I can give you a valid estimate.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think it's far worse to make something up to please mangement and then not make the deadline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="305" OwnerDisplayName="Mark Biek" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:26:22.623" />
<row Id="23395" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3088" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:27:05.803" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://projecteuler.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Project Euler&lt;/a&gt; has a number of interesting mathematics problems that could provide great material for a beginning programmer to cut her teeth on. The problems begin easy and increase in difficulty and the web is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;amp;lr=&amp;amp;safe=active&amp;amp;q=project+euler+solutions&amp;amp;btnG=Search&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;full of sample solutions in various programming languages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2543" OwnerDisplayName="Jared" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:27:05.803" CommunityOwnedDate="2008-09-19T11:43:53.757" />
<row Id="23396" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23205" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:27:35.973" Score="1" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;To add to TimK's answer, if you have a router, test pulling the upstream link on the router, this will test a bad connection without your system knowing that you lost the physical link.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also if you plug it back in after a few seconds it's possible that the connection won't be lost*. This can simulate a very high latency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;*this depends on your ISP and your router. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1534" OwnerDisplayName="Michał Piaskowski" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:27:35.973" />
<row Id="23397" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:27:46.767" Score="16" ViewCount="11495" Body="&lt;p&gt;How do I implement some logic that will allow me to reproduce on Windows the functionality that I have on Linux with the &lt;code&gt;fork()&lt;/code&gt; system call, using Python?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm specifically trying to execute a method on the SAPI Com component, while continuing the other logic in the main thread without blocking or waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2555" OwnerDisplayName="RJBrady" LastEditorUserId="319931" LastEditorDisplayName="ΤΖΩΤΖΙΟΥ" LastEditDate="2012-11-24T07:22:57.633" LastActivityDate="2012-12-04T09:38:37.707" Title="What's the best way to duplicate fork() in windows?" Tags="&lt;python&gt;&lt;windows&gt;&lt;processes&gt;&lt;fork&gt;&lt;subprocess&gt;" AnswerCount="7" FavoriteCount="7" />
<row Id="23398" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:28:06.737" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Object-oriented_analysis_and_design&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;OOAD&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unified_Modeling_Language&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;UML&lt;/a&gt; maybe...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ooo! And &lt;a href=&quot;http://domaindrivendesign.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;DDD&lt;/a&gt; - definitely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Yes, I just had to throw in the obligatory Wikipedia links! It is my first time doing so, and now I feel dirty!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1790" OwnerDisplayName="JasonBunting" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:28:06.737" />
<row Id="23399" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23432" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:28:38.887" Score="0" ViewCount="194" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've got an interesting design question.  I'm designing the security side of our project, to allow us to have different versions of the program for different costs and also to allow Manager-type users to grant or deny access to parts of the program to other users.  Its going to web-based and hosted on our servers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm using a simple Allow or Deny option for each 'Resource' or screen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We're going to have a large number of resources, and the user will be able to set up many different groups to put users in to control access.  Each user can only belong to a single group.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've got two approaches to this in mind, and was curious which would be better for the SQL server in terms of performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Option A&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;The presence of an entry in the access table means access is allowed.  This will not need a column in the database to store information.  If no results are returned, then access is denied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think this will mean a smaller table, but would queries search the whole table to determine there is no match?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Option B&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;A bit column is included in the database that controls the Allow/Deny.  This will mean there is always a result to be found, and makes for a larger table.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1470" OwnerDisplayName="Tilendor" LastEditorUserId="426671" LastEditorDisplayName="Tilendor" LastEditDate="2013-06-25T20:05:40.527" LastActivityDate="2013-06-25T20:05:40.527" Title="Is it better to structure an SQL table to have a match, or return no result" Tags="&lt;sql&gt;&lt;optimization&gt;" AnswerCount="4" />
<row Id="23402" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23417" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:30:04.017" Score="6" ViewCount="2185" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anything thats as good and as stable and as feature-rich as gigaspaces?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2554" OwnerDisplayName="Marcel" LastActivityDate="2013-08-11T02:35:32.870" Title="Are there any alternatives to Gigaspaces?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;java-ee&gt;&lt;gigaspaces&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="23403" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:30:30.070" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yeah, the more I get into software, I start to see myself focusing less on the language and more on the design..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yeah there are framework bits we need to get our head around but most of the time ( &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; not all ) you can look those up as-and-when you need them..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But a good design head? That takes years of experience to start getting it working right..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that is what the companies really pay for.. &quot;Build it and they will come&quot; and all that...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="832" OwnerDisplayName="Rob Cooper" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:30:30.070" />
<row Id="23404" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:30:57.917" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Fixing bugs is generally something that goes into the testing phases of a project, which should not try to schedule things by task.  If the bug is in production, any time spent on it should fall outside the scope of scheduled project activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have to explain that until you know what the problem is, there is no possible way to know how long it will take to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Project management's role in bug fixing should be limited to prioritizing the bug, and then checking progress, not trying to fit it into a Gannt chart.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1219" OwnerDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:30:57.917" />
<row Id="23405" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:31:17.820" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why don't you swap stacks and look at the LAMP stack?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or how about a functional language like haskell?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or write a DSL?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or an app for your phone?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1116" OwnerDisplayName="John Nolan" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:31:17.820" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23406" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23373" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:31:22.390" Score="20" Body="&lt;p&gt;In your Flex SDK folders you should see a 'runtimes\player\win\FlashPlayer.exe' which is a stand alone Flash player.  Open your SWF with that and you'll see a 'Create Projector...' menu item in the File menu which will create the stand-alone EXE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2508" OwnerDisplayName="imaginaryboy" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:31:22.390" />
<row Id="23407" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:31:42.297" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;You give an insane time-frame as an answer. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Two months&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;TWO MONTHS!!??&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;You can have 'I don't know', or you can have 'two months'. Your pick.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Depending on how contentious this gets, it is best to do this via e-mail. Some project managers (especially if you are consulting) will just make something up if you do this. The ideal outcome is &quot;fine, keep working on it and keep me posted daily on progress&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:31:42.297" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23408" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:31:59.783" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Subversion with tortoisesvn. (tortoisesvn because you can see a lot of what goes on visually and will provide a good jumping off point for the command line stuff. ) There is tons of documentation out there and most likely you will see it at least one point in your career. Almost every company I have worked for and interviewed with runs SVN. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1632" OwnerDisplayName="Maudite" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:31:59.783" />
<row Id="23412" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:33:13.027" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think Windows' built-in Task Scheduler is the suggested tool for this job.  That requires an outside application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1490" OwnerDisplayName="Nick" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:33:13.027" />
<row Id="23413" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23399" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:33:56.567" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would vote for Option B.  If you go with Option A and the assumption that if a user exists, they can get in, then you'll eventually run into the problem that you'll want to deny access to a user, without removing the user record.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There will be lots of cases where you'll want to lock a user out, but won't want to completely destroy their account.  One such instance (not necessarily linked to your use case), is when you fail to pay, and they cut off your account until you start paying again.  They don't want to delete the record, because they still want to enable it when you pay up again, instead of recreating the account from scratch, and losing all user history.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:33:56.567" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23414" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23397" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:34:00.747" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Possibly a version of spawn() for python? &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spawn_(operating_system)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spawn_(operating_system)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2016" OwnerDisplayName="Magic Hat" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:34:00.747" />
<row Id="23415" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:34:37.063" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;As you continue to gain more experience in ASP.Net, C#, etc - it's always good to go check out the competition and see if it sparks ideas on how you can do things better in what you're doing.  Taking a look at something like Rails or Django might change how you look at designing or building your apps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2555" OwnerDisplayName="RJBrady" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:34:37.063" />
<row Id="23416" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23399" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:35:30.510" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;B. It allows for much better checks whether the data is complete (for example, when you add an allowable/deniable feature).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, table size should only be a consideration for tables that you know will contain many records (as in, 100,000+). You even taking the time to type the table size consideration into this question already cost more than the extra hard drive space it would take.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:35:30.510" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23417" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23402" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:35:55.970" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Gigaspaces is top notch as far as a Javaspaces implementation goes for scalability and performance. Are you restricted to a Javaspaces implementation? Blitz Javaspaces is top notch for a free product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12081" OwnerDisplayName="Brad Barker" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:35:55.970" />
<row Id="23419" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:36:20.303" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This may or may not be what you're looking for, but read this article, &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.codeproject.com/kb/aspnet/aspnetservice.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Simulate a Windows Service using ASP.NET to run scheduled jobs&lt;/a&gt;&quot;. I think StackOverflow may use this method or it was at least talked about using it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1953" OwnerDisplayName="Jason Shoulders" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:36:20.303" />
<row Id="23420" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:37:35.823" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're now proficient with the languages and technologies you use, then start spending more time focusing on the design, solution architecture, and systems integration. The &quot;bigger picture&quot; that will set you apart from your contemporaries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out some Martin Fowler books like &quot;Patterns of Enterprise Application Architecture&quot;, or Eric Evans' &quot;Domain-Driven Design&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2084" OwnerDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:37:35.823" />
<row Id="23422" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23397" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:38:18.147" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Have a look at the process management functions in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://python.org/doc/2.5/lib/os-process.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;os module&lt;/a&gt;. There are function for starting new processes in many different ways, both synchronously and asynchronously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I should note also that Windows doesn't provide functionality that is exactly like fork() on other systems. To do multiprocessing on Windows, you will need to use the &lt;a href=&quot;http://python.org/doc/2.5/lib/module-threading.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;threading&lt;/a&gt; module.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="893" OwnerDisplayName="Greg Hewgill" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:38:18.147" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23423" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:38:19.817" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Maybe learn more about Usability (best practices, testing, etc.) if you haven't already done so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Steve Krug's &quot;Don't Make Me Think&quot; is a good book to start with.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.useit.com/alertbox/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Jakob Nielsen&lt;/a&gt; always has interesting stuff as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2505" OwnerDisplayName="upheaval" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:38:19.817" />
<row Id="23425" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23373" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:38:23.107" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;imaginaryboy gets it right, I believe. Btw, since you don't have Flex Builder, you might look into the free and open source FlashDevelop if you're on Windows. It's my favorite environment for developing anything Actionscript (the Flex support is pretty great, too).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1344" OwnerDisplayName="Brian Warshaw" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:38:23.107" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23426" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23228" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:38:40.767" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well I guess you have to be rather particular about it, but like people are saying, it makes more sense for String.Format to be static because of the implied semantics. Consider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot;Hello {0}&quot;.Format(&quot;World&quot;); // this makes it sound like Format *modifies* &#xA;                             // the string, which is not possible as &#xA;                             // strings are immutable.&#xA;&#xA;string[] parts = &quot;Hello World&quot;.Split(' ');    // this however sounds right, &#xA;                                             // because it implies that you &#xA;                                             // split an existing string into &#xA;                                             // two *new* strings.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1710" OwnerDisplayName="Fredrik Kalseth" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="  " LastEditDate="2008-08-23T00:43:02.723" LastActivityDate="2008-08-23T00:43:02.723" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="23430" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23310" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:39:40.390" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I found &lt;a href=&quot;http://unfuddle.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://unfuddle.com&lt;/a&gt; saved me messing about with installing SVN or git. You can get a free account in there and use either of those - plus you can use your OpenID there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then you avoid having to mess about setting it up right and focus on how you're going to use it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2362" OwnerDisplayName="Brabster" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:39:40.390" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="23431" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23370" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:40:17.970" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are a few ambiguities in your question. What operation needs to be successful?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For everything you want to know about drag and drop, browse through these search results (multiple pages worth):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/search?q=drag+drop+site%3Ablogs.msdn.com%2Foldnewthing&amp;amp;rls=com.microsoft:en-us&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;amp;startIndex=&amp;amp;startPage=1&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Raymond Chen on drag and drop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="414" OwnerDisplayName="Stu" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:40:17.970" />
<row Id="23432" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23399" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:41:25.190" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;If it's only going to be Allow/Deny, then a simple linking table between Users and Resources would work fine.  If there is an entry keyed to the User-Resource in the linking table, allow access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;UserResources&#xA;-------------&#xA;UserId FK-&amp;gt;Users&#xA;ResourceId FK-&amp;gt;Resources&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and the sql would be something like &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if exists (select 1 from UserResources &#xA;where UserId = @uid and ResourceId=@rid)&#xA;set @allow=1;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a clustered index on (UserId and ResourceId), the query would be blindingly fast even with millions of records.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1219" OwnerDisplayName="Eric Z Beard" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:41:25.190" />
<row Id="23433" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23098" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:42:00.947" Score="1" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I think this is true to some extent. However, when you license under the GPL, you have the option to say, &quot;Version 2&quot;, &quot;Version 2 or later&quot;. If you're leary about how the license may change in the future, you are free to just say it is licensed under that specific version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That opens up a different can of worms, though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you released under GPL2 &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; and GPL3 comes out and you &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; the changes it makes, you're theoretically going to have to go around to all your contributors and get their unanimous approval to change the license their code is released under.  All it takes is one of them to say &quot;nope, I only licensed my contributions under GPL2 and refuse to permit GPL3&quot; - or they can just not reply - to derail your proposed license change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1902010" OwnerDisplayName="ceejayoz" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:42:00.947" />
<row Id="23435" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23250" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:42:19.137" Score="98" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't mean this to sound snarky, but it doesn't matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Look at the things that are important: your project, your code, your job, your personal life. None of them are going to have their success rest on whether or not you use the &quot;this&quot; keyword to qualify access to fields. The this keyword will not help you ship on time. It's not going to reduce bugs, it's not going to have any appreciable effect on code quality or maintainability. It's not going to get you a raise, or allow you to spend less time at the office. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's really just a style issue. If you like &quot;this&quot;, then use it. If you don't, then don't. If you need it to get correct semantics then use it. The truth is, every programmer has his own unique programing style. That style reflects that particular programmer's notions of what the &quot;most aesthetically pleasing code&quot; should look like. By definition, any other programmer who reads your code is going to have a different programing style. That means there is always going to be something you did that the other guy doesn't like, or would have done differently. At some point some guy is going to read your code and grumble about something. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wouldn't fret over it. I would just make sure the code is as aesthetically pleasing as possible according to your own tastes. If you ask 10 programmers how to format code, you are going to get about 15 different opinions. A better thing to focus on is how the code is factored. Are things abstracted right? Did I pick meaningful names for things? Is there a lot of code duplication? Are there ways I can simplify stuff? Getting those things right, I think, will have the greatest positive impact on your project, your code, your job, and your life. Coincidentally, it will probably also cause the other guy to grumble the least. If your code works, is easy to read, and is well factored, the other guy isn't going to be scrutinizing how you initialize fields. He's just going to use your code, marvel at it's greatness, and then move on to something else.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1737192" OwnerDisplayName="Scott Wisniewski" LastEditorUserId="516138" LastEditorDisplayName="Scott Wisniewski" LastEditDate="2011-03-16T09:27:03.470" LastActivityDate="2011-03-16T09:27:03.470" CommentCount="6" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-16T11:38:04.327" />
<row Id="23436" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23370" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:42:23.770" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;So, you intend to modify the data being dropped based on the drop target?  I don't think this is possible; after all, you populate the data when the drag is initiated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1490" OwnerDisplayName="Nick" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:42:23.770" />
<row Id="23439" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25899" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:44:55.150" Score="1" ViewCount="2043" Body="&lt;p&gt;My website is entirely flash based, it moves around a 3D model which was given to me as chunks of video that I've converted to FLV files. I'm using the FLVPlayback component to control the video inside of my program. While running memory checks using System.totalMemory I've noticed that whenever a video is loaded, it will eat up a chunk of memory and even when I remove all the event listeners from it(they are all weakly referenced), remove the component from its parent, stop the video and null the component instance, it still will not give that memory back.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This has been bothering me since I started working on this project because of the huge amount of video a user can potentially instantiate and load. Currently every video is loaded into a new FLVPlayback instance whenever it is required, but I have read that perhaps the best way to go about this problem is to simply have a global FLVPlayback instance and just reload the new video into the old instance, that way there would only be one FLVPlayback component in the application's memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else run into this problem as well? Have you found a better solution than using a global instance that you just re-use for every new video? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1945" OwnerDisplayName="vanhornRF" LastActivityDate="2009-12-10T19:45:14.477" Title="FLVPlayback component memory issues" Tags="&lt;flash&gt;&lt;actionscript-3&gt;&lt;memory&gt;&lt;video&gt;&lt;swf&gt;" AnswerCount="5" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="23440" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:45:26.133" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;I love asking my PM, &quot;How long does it take to find your keys when you lose them?&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Honestly it depends on how critical the bug is and how many critical bugs you have.  If this is THE high priority bug, then you keep troubleshooting and keep the PM informed.  If this is not the critical bug, then it should be common sense to your PM that you can mark this one as &quot;expensive to fix&quot; and come back to it when he can allow more time in the schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There has to be a level of trust from the PM for your estimates or this situation will become common.  However you handle this - you will be setting the expectations for the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2555" OwnerDisplayName="RJBrady" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:45:26.133" />
<row Id="23441" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23382" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:46:18.347" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;If we're talking Microsoft platform, then I'd always develop a separate Windows Service to handle such batch tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can always reference the same assemblies that are being used by your web application to avoid any nasty code duplication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2084" OwnerDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastEditorUserId="2084" LastEditorDisplayName="Ian Nelson" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T21:05:34.197" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T21:05:34.197" />
<row Id="23442" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23190" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:46:19.110" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;This kind of thing is much easier if you use STL containers, or maybe &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.boost.org/libs/multi_array/doc/index.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Boost.MultiArray&lt;/a&gt;. But if you must use an array:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#include &amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&#xA;#include &amp;lt;boost/foreach.hpp&amp;gt;&#xA;#include &amp;lt;vector&amp;gt;&#xA;&#xA;int sum(int x) {&#xA;    return x;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;class T, unsigned N&amp;gt;&#xA;int sum(const T (&amp;amp;x)[N]) {&#xA;    int r = 0;&#xA;    for(int i = 0; i &amp;lt; N; ++i) {&#xA;        r += sum(x[i]);&#xA;    }&#xA;    return r;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;class T, unsigned N&amp;gt;&#xA;std::vector&amp;lt;int&amp;gt; reduce(const T (&amp;amp;x)[N]) {&#xA;    std::vector&amp;lt;int&amp;gt; result;&#xA;    for(int i = 0; i &amp;lt; N; ++i) {&#xA;        result.push_back(sum(x[i]));&#xA;    }&#xA;    return result;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;int main() {&#xA;    int x[][2][2] = {&#xA;        { { 1, 2 }, { 3, 4 } },&#xA;        { { 5, 6 }, { 7, 8 } }&#xA;    };&#xA;&#xA;    BOOST_FOREACH(int v, reduce(x)) {&#xA;        std::cout&amp;lt;&amp;lt;v&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&quot;\n&quot;;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2434" OwnerDisplayName="Daniel James" LastEditorUserId="2434" LastEditorDisplayName="Daniel James" LastEditDate="2008-08-22T21:19:16.893" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T21:19:16.880" />
<row Id="23445" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:47:16.520" Score="26" ViewCount="67542" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have two collections of the same object, &lt;code&gt;Collection&amp;lt;Foo&amp;gt; oldSet&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Collection&amp;lt;Foo&amp;gt; newSet&lt;/code&gt;.  The required logic is as follow:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;if &lt;code&gt;foo&lt;/code&gt; is in(*) &lt;code&gt;oldSet&lt;/code&gt; but not &lt;code&gt;newSet&lt;/code&gt;, call &lt;code&gt;doRemove(foo)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;else if &lt;code&gt;foo&lt;/code&gt; is not in &lt;code&gt;oldSet&lt;/code&gt; but in &lt;code&gt;newSet&lt;/code&gt;, call &lt;code&gt;doAdd(foo)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;else if &lt;code&gt;foo&lt;/code&gt; is in both collections but modified, call &lt;code&gt;doUpdate(oldFoo, newFoo)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;else if &lt;code&gt;!foo.activated &amp;amp;&amp;amp; foo.startDate &amp;gt;= now&lt;/code&gt;, call &lt;code&gt;doStart(foo)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;else if &lt;code&gt;foo.activated &amp;amp;&amp;amp; foo.endDate &amp;lt;= now&lt;/code&gt;, call &lt;code&gt;doEnd(foo)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(*) &quot;in&quot; means the unique identifier matches, not necessarily the content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The current (legacy) code does many comparisons to figure out &lt;code&gt;removeSet&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;addSet&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;updateSet&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;startSet&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;endSet&lt;/code&gt;, and then loop to act on each item.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The code is quite messy (partly because I have left out some spaghetti logic already) and I am trying to refactor it.  Some more background info:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As far as I know, the &lt;code&gt;oldSet&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;newSet&lt;/code&gt; are actually backed by &lt;code&gt;ArrayList&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Each set contains less than 100 items, most likely max out at 20&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This code is called frequently (measured in millions/day), although the sets seldom differ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If I convert &lt;code&gt;oldSet&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;newSet&lt;/code&gt; into &lt;code&gt;HashMap&amp;lt;Foo&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; (order is not of concern here), with the IDs as keys, would it made the code easier to read and easier to compare?  How much of time &amp;amp; memory performance is loss on the conversion?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Would iterating the two sets and perform the appropriate operation be more efficient and concise?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2551" OwnerDisplayName="sundae1888" LastActivityDate="2013-07-22T13:33:01.703" Title="How Best to Compare Two Collections in Java and Act on Them?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;collections&gt;" AnswerCount="7" FavoriteCount="6" />
<row Id="23446" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23473" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:48:03.897" Score="10" ViewCount="8570" Body="&lt;p&gt;Have just started using Visual Studio Professional's built-in unit testing features, which as I understand, uses MS Test to run the tests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The .trx file that the tests produce is xml, but was wondering if there was an easy way to convert this file into a more &quot;manager-friendly&quot; format?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My ultimate goal is to be able to automate the unit-testing and be able to produce a nice looking document that shows the tests run and how 100% of them passed  :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="443" OwnerDisplayName="PaulStock" LastEditorUserId="2134" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2008-08-23T20:02:47.257" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T15:47:16.327" Title="How do I format Visual Studio Test results file (.trx) into a more readable format?" Tags="&lt;visual-studio-2008&gt;&lt;unit-testing&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="23448" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="24167" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:48:14.003" Score="6" ViewCount="1844" Body="&lt;p&gt;does anyone here have ever worked with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com.br/url?sa=t&amp;amp;ct=res&amp;amp;cd=1&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FDomain-specific_programming_language&amp;amp;ei=QyWvSIXcC4foebjSlHs&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFsZOnJm-AGmi5sxai8YI-0Al6wfA&amp;amp;sig2=6nX5EkUmNkEwiSKAkUeyZQ&quot;&gt;DSLs (Domain Specific Languages)&lt;/a&gt; in the finance domain ? I am planning to introduce some kind of DSL support in the application i'm working on and would like to share some ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am in a stage of identifying which are the most stable domain elements and selecting the feature which would be better implemented with the dsl. I haven't yet defined the syntax for this first feature. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I appreciate any advices&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gustavo&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2015" OwnerDisplayName="Gustavo" LastActivityDate="2013-05-05T17:30:06.850" Title="DSL in Finance" Tags="&lt;dsl&gt;&lt;finance&gt;" AnswerCount="4" FavoriteCount="6" />
<row Id="23449" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:48:14.380" Score="0" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I love asking my PM, &quot;How long does it&#xA;  take to find your keys when you lose&#xA;  them?&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love that! I will definitely use that one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1627" OwnerDisplayName="Ryan Farley" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:48:14.380" />
<row Id="23450" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23388" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:48:36.127" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If the PM won't take 'don't know' for an answer, then I would suggest that you tell him that you are not done with your analysis yet. And if he asks how much longer the analysis will take, you can tell that you don't know. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="380" OwnerDisplayName="Vaibhav" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:48:36.127" />
<row Id="23452" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23375" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:49:25.983" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't program is Visual Foxpro nor have I, but Jeff and Joel talked about that language in one of their podcasts. From what I remember, they said it was a decent tool for its time, but is highly outdated now. Could you convert it to something more modern? Frankly, if any of my clients, who I made applications for in Classic ASP, contacted me for updates, I'd upgrade everything to .NET. To stay relevant and effective, you have to ante up eventually. That's been one of my biggest frustrations with programming and web development. At the same time, it's one of the best things about programming and web development because the technology is theoretically always getting better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1953" OwnerDisplayName="Jason Shoulders" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:49:25.983" />
<row Id="23456" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22309" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:50:52.237" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago I found an ARM disassembler I used while doing some embedded work. However, I don't remember its name - though I think it was part of a larger package like an emulator or something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In your case, could you ask your compiler to generate an assembly listing of the compiled code? That might help give you some scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Failing that, you could break up your function into one or more new functions, if all you can get is the stack trace. Then break up the new function into one or more again. This is the tried-and-true &quot;divide and conquer&quot; method. And if you have 35 calls to memset() in one function, it might be a good idea from a design standpoint too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Update: I found the package I used: &lt;a href=&quot;http://armphetamine.sourceforge.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ARMphetamine&lt;/a&gt;. It worked for the ARM9 code I was developing, but it looks like it hasn't been updated in quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="893" OwnerDisplayName="Greg Hewgill" LastEditorUserId="893" LastEditorDisplayName="Greg Hewgill" LastEditDate="2008-09-13T01:51:53.303" LastActivityDate="2008-09-13T01:51:53.303" />
<row Id="23457" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:51:40.847" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;@ Michael DSL=&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domain-specific_programming_language&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Domain Specific Language&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for what you should learn, that depends on what you're interested in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to challenge yourself while staying in the same medium (web-centric applications)? I would suggest learning about Apache and the LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP) architecture and challenge yourself to build a web application that you could readily build with ASP .NET using it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to learn something completely different? Try &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swi-prolog.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Prolog&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://common-lisp.net/project/lispbox/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;LISP&lt;/a&gt; and see what you can do with those.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe you'd like to get into embedded software? Learn C to start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have a wide variety of ways to improve your skills, and each one has career paths attached to them. (Well, maybe not Prolog, but it's fun!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1429" OwnerDisplayName="Marcus" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:51:40.847" />
<row Id="23460" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23098" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:52:18.723" Score="0" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If you released under GPL2 only and&#xA;  GPL3 comes out and you like the&#xA;  changes it makes, you're theoretically&#xA;  going to have to go around to all your&#xA;  contributors and get their unanimous&#xA;  approval to change the license their&#xA;  code is released under. All it takes&#xA;  is one of them to say &quot;nope, I only&#xA;  licensed my contributions under GPL2&#xA;  and refuse to permit GPL3&quot; - or they&#xA;  can just not reply - to derail your&#xA;  proposed license change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which brings up some other questions. Do you plan to accept patches from outside developers?  When you do accept patches do you requires patch submitters to hand over copyright also?  If they don't transfer copyright, how does that allow you to change your own license for future considerations.  If there was a project with their own license and I was going to release a bunch of code to it, it stated that it was licensed under XYX version N, or any future version, then what's to say that the people controlling that license won't do a complete 180 on a future version, and make it completely closed source?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1862" OwnerDisplayName="Kibbee" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:52:18.723" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="23463" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23391" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:53:18.157" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;The more languages you know, the more marketable you are. Look and see what the more popular (market for, not fan base) languages are, then add on some cutting edge tech that is not in much use yet, rounded out by general programming skill.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With your skill set I would recommend (as far as languages):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Java as a starting point  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For .Net add in the .Net MVC (you have LINQ or that would be here also)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Language agnostic skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Design Patterns (includes the MVC)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Domain Driven Design&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test Driven Design&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1215" OwnerDisplayName="Carlton Jenke" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:53:18.157" />
<row Id="23466" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23217" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:55:32.333" Score="0" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Basically, is there any appreciable difference between: &lt;code&gt;onchange=&quot;javascript: myFunction(this)&quot;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;onchange=&quot;myFunction(this)&quot;&lt;/code&gt; ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assuming you meant &lt;code&gt;href=&quot;javascript: myFunction(this)&quot;&lt;/code&gt;, yes there is, especially when loading content using the javascript. Using the javascript: pseudo protocol makes the content inaccessible to some humans and all search engines, whereas using a real href and then changing the behaviour of the link using javascript makes the content accessible if javascript is turned off or not available in the particular client.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" OwnerDisplayName="Flubba" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:55:32.333" />
<row Id="23468" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22976" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:56:44.997" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Both answers were very helpful! Here's what I ended up with: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if( typeof( rpNameSpace ) == &quot;undefined&quot; ) rpNameSpace = {};&#xA;&#xA;rpNameSpace.foo = function()&#xA;{&#xA;    this.length = 613;&#xA;}&#xA;rpNameSpace.foo.prototype.getLength = function()&#xA;{&#xA;    return this.length * 2;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, to use the resulting &quot;namespaced&quot; object:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    var x = new rpNameSpace.foo()&#xA;&#xA;    display( x.getLength() );&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you both very much.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;rp&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2536" OwnerDisplayName="rogerpence" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:56:44.997" />
<row Id="23469" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="23445" CreationDate="2008-08-22T20:57:38.663" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;For a set that small is generally not worth it to convert from an Array to a HashMap/set.  In fact, you're probably best off keeping them in an array and then sorting them by key and iterating over both lists simultaneously to do the comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1247" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Deck" LastActivityDate="2008-08-22T20:57:38.663" />